thank you everybody for coming um I need
谢谢大家来我需要
a photo so you guys just all I just need
一张照片，你们就是我所需要的
you to say open source now can you just
你说开源现在可以
say that before we take a photo one -
说，在我们拍照之前-
Ana oh that's so good that's so money
安娜哦，太好了，这么多钱
thank you so good now then up this is
谢谢你，现在太好了，这就是
the amazing the the without parallel the
惊人的无与伦比的
incredible dr. sire he's a paying
令人难以置信的博士父亲，他是有偿的
attention to the code not to us that's
注意代码而不是我们
why we like him and I'm Josh hi my name
为什么我们喜欢他，我叫乔希，我叫我
is Josh long uh doctor sire I'm gonna
是乔希吗，我要父亲
call him dr. cloud native he's a you
叫他博士。云原生他是你
want to tell us about yourself talk uh
想告诉我们有关你自己的话题吧
you can read write huh
你可以读写吧
he's one of the one of the contributors
他是贡献者之一
to spring the co-founder of spring batch
Spring Spring联合创始人
co-founder of spring security Oh off
Spring Security的联合创始人哦
spring boot and spring cloud basically
弹簧靴和弹簧云基本上
he gets what we're trying to do here and
他得到了我们在这里想要做的事情，
then he tells us what we're trying to do
然后他告诉我们我们要做什么
um uh I'm a spring guy oh yeah some
嗯，我是个春天的家伙，哦，是的，有些
spring so thank you for joining me today
春天，谢谢你今天加入我
doc come he's gonna make sure I don't
博士来他要确保我不
screw this up my role here is to slow
搞砸了我的角色是要慢
him down if it's all possible right so I
如果一切都对，他就倒下，所以我
might need some help if anybody has a
如果有人有可能需要一些帮助
question yeah
是的
don't hesitate please me I am uh well
不要犹豫，拜托我，我很好
this is an old irrelevant slide now the
这是一张不相关的旧幻灯片，现在
slide is out of date it's a lie I am a
幻灯片已过期，这是一个谎言，我是
not a defense not the definitive
不是防御不是决定性的
articles an indefinite ative article a
文章不定冠词a
spring developer advocate at pivotal
关键开发人员的春季开发者倡导者
that's my email and my Twitter how many
那是我的电子邮件，我的Twitter有多少
of you are on the Twitter's its 2015 how
你们中的2015年在Twitter上的表现如何
many of you on Twitter's Ted Twitter's
在Twitter的Ted Twitter上的许多人
no one no one nobody awkward okay okay
没有人没人没人尴尬好吧好吧
it's okay well there's this thing my
没关系，这是我的东西
friends
朋友们
Twitter's if you're there let's carry
Twitter的，如果你在那里，那就随身携带
the discussion forward no doubt you're
毫无疑问，你在讨论
gonna leave this room upset and too
也要离开这个房间
perturbed and you want to vent that
困扰，你想发泄
find me on the Twitter's and we'll talk
在Twitter上找到我，我们会谈
we'll talk it out well hug it out um I'm
我们会说出来，好好拥抱，嗯，我是
gonna drop a champion and I open Taurus
要丢下冠军，我打开金牛座
I'm the leading contributor of bugs to
我是bug的主要贡献者
many fine spring projects not
许多美好的春季项目没有
least of which are spring boots spring
最少的是 spring boot
cloud renovation and so on uh and I have
云翻新等等，我有
a special guest because you see we have
一个特别的客人，因为你看到我们有
a special guest but you see the
一个特别的客人，但是你看到
economics of building applications today
当今建筑应用的经济学
they're very different from what they
他们和他们有很大的不同
were 15 years ago when or 13 years ago
在15年前或13年前
when spring started on this adventure
当春天开始冒险时
but yet some things remain remain
但仍然有些事情仍然存在
eternally true so I was hoping to invite
永远真实，所以我希望邀请
dr. Rob Johnson onto the stage to speak
博士罗布·约翰逊（Rob Johnson）登台演讲
about that for just a minute
大约一分钟
or five or whatever you want really
或五个或您真正想要的任何东西
welcome star oh thanks Josh
欢迎明星哦，谢谢乔希
thank you sir oh okay looks better when
谢谢您，先生，好的
it goes on so this is actually the first
它继续，所以这实际上是第一个
time that I've spoken to spring one for
我讲过的春天
five years so it's an interesting
五年，这很有趣
experience and it's great to see I think
经验，很高兴看到我的想法
the largest number of attendees ever and
参加人数最多
as I say look old friends in the spring
正如我所说的在春天看老朋友
community so as Josh says spring goes
就像乔希所说的春天
back a long way
后退很长一段路
yesterday I was walking around
昨天我走来走去
Washington with my old friend Jurgen
华盛顿和我的老友尤尔根（Jurgen）
hello of course as I hope everyone knows
你好，当然，我希望大家都知道
is a legendary coder and I don't use
是一个传奇的编码器，我不使用
that word lightly a legendary coder and
这个词轻轻地变成了传奇的编码器，
you know the heart and soul of Spring
你知道春天的心灵
Framework and has been for something
框架和已经有所作为
like 12 13 years so the yoga and I were
像12到13年，所以我和瑜伽
walking around Washington and a couple
在华盛顿和一对夫妇周围散步
of things that happened was that I got
发生的事情是我得到了
quite sundar Jurgen got a little bit
桑达·尤尔根（Jurgen）颇为乐观
sunburned but I was there more than
被晒伤了，但我在那里比
anybody else but also we were kind of
其他人，但我们也有点
reflecting on the last 13 years and how
回顾过去的13年，以及如何
things have changed so when spring the
事情发生了变化，所以当春天
first code the wedding to spring was
春季婚礼的第一个代码是
published it was of course published my
发表它当然是发表我的
first book as that point
第一本书
30:21 framework it was even pre
30:21它甚至是预先的
open-source so just think about that for
开源的，所以考虑一下
a moment the world of 2002 so in
片刻的2002年世界
Washington you can't avoid thinking
华盛顿，你无法避免的思考
about politics President Bush was early
关于政治布什总统很早
in his first term if don't think it
如果他不认为这是他的第一学期
really occurred to anybody that the next
真的有人想到
Republican president would probably be
共和党总统可能是
Donald Trump and in the technology world
唐纳德·特朗普（Donald Trump）和科技界
things were very very different so at
事情非常不同，所以在
that point I initially can see it's
我最初可以看到的一点是
bring to deal with the truly horrible
应对真正的可怕
complexity of things like EJB to you
EJB之类的复杂性给您
know early WebLogic websphere these
了解这些早期的WebLogic Websphere
healy monolithic application servers
Healy整体应用服务器
that really were designed without the
真正的设计没有
slightest thought about whether
关于是否
developers would actually enjoy life
开发人员实际上会享受生活
where the developers could actually get
开发人员实际上可以得到的地方
anything done and me this was already a
做任何事情，我已经是一个
jaded to EJB one was so bad that he than
厌倦了EJB，他比
I don't remember it but AJ Gator's was
我不记得了，但是AJ Gator的
pretty bad so that was the world where
太糟糕了，那是那个世界
the vision would spring was to make
春天的愿景是使
things simple for developers you know to
对您了解的开发人员而言简单的事情
get that complexity get that boilerplate
获得那种复杂性获得样板
out of the way so developers can
让开发人员可以
actually implement business logic and
实际实施业务逻辑
deliver business value so there were
提供业务价值，因此
really three core ideas that spring was
春天真的是三个核心思想
placed on so this slide is one that I
放在这张幻灯片上，我
actually pulled out of a deck that I had
实际上从我所拥有的甲板上退出
my laptop I believe this is from a talk
我的笔记本电脑，我相信这是从谈话中
that I gave to AT&amp;T st. Louis in 2007
我给AT＆T st。 2007年的路易斯
and this slide was in our trainings it
这张幻灯片在我们的培训中
was in a whole lot of talks that I and
我和我在很多谈话中
how the papers gave and I young and just
论文如何给我，我年轻而公正
mentioned that he sometimes brings you
提到他有时会带你
slide on as well as you can say it's not
滑上去，你可以说不是
even spring so it's branded it is an e
即使是春天，所以它的品牌是e
to face 21 branded which was the
面对21个品牌
original name of the SpringSource entity
SpringSource实体的原始名称
so essentially there were three core
所以基本上有三个核心
ideas that's previous build around
之前的想法
dependency injection externalized
外部依赖注入
configuration ioneiy externalized some
配置离子化一些
behaviors like transaction management a
交易管理之类的行为
whole bunch of other things and do it so
一堆其他的事情，这样做
that it doesn't complicate it or covet
它不会使它复杂化或令人垂涎
and finally portable service abstraction
最后是可移植服务抽象
so for example if you're going to do
因此，例如，如果您要
transaction management it's great to
交易管理很棒
have a transparent using AOP but how is
有一个透明的使用AOP，但如何
it going to work
它会工作
how is it going to be guaranteed to work
如何保证能正常工作
really robustly in every environment by
在每个环境中都非常强大
the way the answer to that last question
最后一个问题的答案
is how is it guaranteed to work really
如何保证它真正起作用
robustly is your good hello is in the
可靠的是，您好吗？
blue shirt at the back and other side so
背面和另一侧的蓝色衬衫
you know these three key I use to spring
你知道我用的这三个关键
are equally true today so when we look
今天同样如此，所以当我们看
at the world today obviously we're not
在当今世界上，我们显然不是
we're not thinking about President Bush
我们不是在考虑布什总统
with thinking about president Truong and
想着总统Truong和
we're in a world where some of those old
我们生活在一个古老的世界
problems I've got right where logic
我正确的问题在哪里逻辑
WebSphere you know I I think that even
您知道的WebSphere II甚至认为
without you know IBM and Oracle they
没有您了解IBM和Oracle
know those products of get Brett the
知道布雷特的那些产品
monolithic app server is history even
单片应用服务器甚至是历史
the primary role of things like Tomcat
Tomcat之类的主要角色
is you know really hot visible things
你知道真的很热的东西吗
that's also a diminishing because it's
这也在减少，因为
all going to be about micro services
一切都将与微服务有关
it's really the whole notion of the
这实际上是整个概念
monolithic server is becoming irrelevant
单片服务器变得无关紧要
but the interesting thing is despite all
但有趣的是，尽管
this change these three core ideas
这改变了这三个核心思想
behind spring and of course a lot of
在春天之后，当然还有很多
very fine code that implements them are
实现它们的非常好的代码是
equally relevant so for example when we
同样重要，例如当我们
think about the world of cloud it's an
想想云的世界
exciting world but it's all great it's
激动人心的世界，但这真是太好了
all shiny and you just go and try to use
所有闪亮，你就去尝试使用
for example some of the Netflix and
例如Netflix和
other projects without using spring but
其他项目不使用spring但是
it's pretty fun and what you'll find is
这很有趣，您会发现
you're writing a whole lot of blood flow
你正在写大量的血液
it won't be there
它不会在那里
you know things like JDI lookups that we
您知道诸如JDI查找之类的事情
had to do by hand before spring existed
在春天存在之前必须手工做
so essentially those core ideas are
所以本质上那些核心思想是
still bearing fruit today and obviously
今天仍然结出果实，显然
the very awesome spring team very
非常棒的春季团队
awesome spring community are the key
很棒的春季社区是关键
people behind that and it's exciting to
背后的人，这令人兴奋
me that I think a new string to Springs
我，我认为斯普林斯的新弦乐
has been added so for example when you
已添加，例如当您
look at spring book there is this a
看春书有这本
regional theme of simplification is
简化的区域主题是
still there in spades
仍然黑桃
but there's actually in you that you
但实际上你里面有你
approach it you know defaulting
接近您知道的默认值
simplifying configuration radically so
从根本上简化配置，因此
you know I think it preserves all these
你知道我认为它保留了所有这些
key values and add something else which
键值并添加其他内容
continues that spring mission so you
继续那个春季任务，所以你
know when I look at spring berg spring
知道当我看着春天伯格春天
cloud in particular today to me very
今天对我来说尤其是乌云
much seems like continuing the mission
似乎在继续执行任务
the mission and I guess to to to pursue
任务，我想去追求
the political analogy since it is
政治类比，因为它是
inevitable here the state of the spring
春天在这里不可避免
union is holding so with that I won't
工会正在举行，以至于我不会
take up any more time I'll hand over to
花更多的时间我会交给
my friends Dave and Josh
我的朋友戴夫和乔希
Dave I think I first worked within maybe
戴夫，我想我可能先在
2005 yeah and you joined interface 21
2005年，您加入了Interface 21
thing in 2006 7-7 it wasn't somebody
在2006年7月7日发生的事情
else's savings and somebody fed up a
别人的积蓄，有人厌倦了
bomb clear no 205 doesn't get somebody's
炸弹清除没有205没有得到某人的
head up above MFM Oh fine oh that's
朝着MFM前进，哦，好，那是
yes London yeah yes we actually first
是的，伦敦，是的，我们实际上是第一个
spent a significant amount of time
花了大量时间
together in a meeting room which we
一起在会议室里
couldn't Lee
李不能
since April London was shut down and I
自四月伦敦关闭以来，我
haven't known Josh quite as quite as
还不太了解乔希
long but you know immensely impressed by
很久了，但您知道给您留下深刻的印象
his enthusiasm in what he's accomplished
他对成就的热情
in the sprint community thank you guys
在sprint社区中，谢谢大家
thanks rod
感谢棒
thank you it's it's really good to hear
谢谢你，真的很高兴听到
rod say that cuz yeah it's kind of
竿说那是因为
that's what I felt that when I was
那就是我当时的感受
writing bits of spring boot and spring
编写弹簧靴和弹簧的位
cloud I was thinking this must be what
云，我当时想这一定是
it felt like for rod you know at the
感觉就像你在
beginning it must have been like this
开始一定是这样的
and basically that's what he's saying
基本上这就是他的意思
we've done the right thing
我们做对了
so thanks rod Thank You rod okay all
所以谢谢杆谢谢杆好的
right so um moving on a little bit uh
对，所以嗯，继续前进吧
dr. syenite we work at pivotal right and
博士syenite我们在关键的地方工作，
we spend a lot of time talking to users
我们花很多时间与用户交谈
to developers to customers who are
对开发人员，对
trying to build applications and we've
尝试构建应用程序，我们已经
seen that while they recognize the value
看到他们认识到价值
of of moving to an automated platform to
迁移到自动化平台的过程
reduce the waste that you you find in
减少您发现的浪费
so-called water scrum fall silos is
所谓的水乱落筒仓是
where you have agile development being
你在哪里敏捷开发
done by the software people but then you
由软件人员完成，但随后您
have waste around the edges on the
浪费在边缘上
before and after and it takes time it
之前和之后，这需要时间
reduces our sorry it increases clock
减少了我们的遗憾，它增加了时钟
time to deployment we see customers
部署时间，我们看到客户
struggling to get their code out there
努力使他们的代码在那里
and faster right and so we we know that
和更快的权利，所以我们知道
in order for them to get their code out
为了让他们得到他们的代码
there faster and to be able to handle
那里更快并且能够处理
more developers working on their code
更多的开发人员在处理他们的代码
there is a threshold a line that you
有一个门槛，你
have to you have to find where it's
必须要找到它的位置
convenient to write software and then
方便地编写软件然后
deploy it and involve it without being
部署它并让它参与其中
gated by synchronization changes from
由同步变更控制
other people right there's also scale
其他人也有规模
capacity demands people are trying to
人们要求的容量需求
build applications to meet a much larger
构建应用程序以满足更大的需求
audience than they were before thanks to
观众比以前多了
drivers like social and like mobile
社交和移动等司机
right these things mean that the
对，这些事情意味着
Internet is not just the desktop browser
互联网不仅仅是桌面浏览器
it means that anybody walking around in
这意味着任何人走进来
their pockets could be a device making
他们的口袋可能是一个设备
lots of requests all the time we also
一直有很多要求
see that as domains and applications get
看到域和应用程序得到
more complex
更复杂
and more sophisticated the consistency
更复杂的一致性
of the domain the crispness of the
域的脆度
domain starts to blur as you start to
开始时域开始模糊
add more to the edges so all of these
添加更多的边缘，所以所有这些
reasons and more are reasons that people
原因以及更多是人们的原因
are moving to this microservices model
正在转向这种微服务模型
they have an automatic platform but
他们有一个自动平台，但是
they're trying to write software to
他们正在尝试编写软件来
fully exploit that platform and that's
充分利用该平台，那就是
what microservices gives you gives you
微服务能给您带来什么
the ability to write small singly
小写能力
focused services that work well that
重点突出的服务，效果很好
explains point this cloud platform
解释点这个云平台
however distributed computing is not
但是分布式计算不是
easy right
容易的权利
and there's pain when you when you move
当你移动时会有痛苦
to this world and naturally this is one
这个世界，自然而然地
place where we hope that spring cloud
我们希望春天有云的地方
which is built on spring boot can help
建立在弹簧靴上可以帮助
spring cloud integrates sort of the best
Spring Cloud整合了最好的
of read patterns that the Giants of the
的巨人的阅读模式
web have sort of discovered for us with
网络已经为我们发现了
their massive R&amp;D budgets and their
他们庞大的研发预算及其
massive engineering investment now we
现在我们进行了大量的工程投资
the mere mortals you know we can take
你知道我们可以接受的凡人
Prometheus from the likes of Netflix and
来自Netflix和
Twitter and so on and build software the
Twitter等并构建软件
same way that they do as quickly and
他们做得一样快，
agile E as they do so that's we're going
敏捷E，因为他们这样做，这就是我们要去的地方
to talk about today we're going to talk
谈论今天，我们将要谈论
about these patterns that you're going
关于你要走的这些模式
to need to support when you build a
当您建立一个
distributed system I'm going to be
我将成为分布式系统
coding because dr. sire you know he he
编码，因为博士。先生，您知道他他
wrote all the code over years for spring
写下了春季的所有代码
boot and spring cloud along with other
靴子和弹簧云以及其他
very talented people and then he
非常有才华的人，然后他
documented it and made it amazing but I
记录下来，并使其惊人，但我
feel like I'm really doing all the work
觉得我真的在做所有工作
here let's just be clear
这里让我们清楚一点
so we're gonna go and build a new
所以我们要去建立一个新的
application we're gonna go to my my
应用程序，我们要去我的
other favorite place on the web my other
网上其他我最喜欢的地方
favorite place on the web starts up to
网络上最喜欢的地方开始了
bring the real flavor what was your
带来真正的味道是什么
first favorite production Oh like
最喜欢的制作哦喜欢
Disneyland right yeah it's better than
是的，迪士尼乐园比
this land much better um you need Wi-Fi
这个土地好多了，您需要Wi-Fi
for this to work my friends so we may be
为了这个工作我的朋友，所以我们可能是
yes working here right yeah what's the
是的，在这里工作对，是什么
password STG X okay if you got this but
密码STG X知道，但是
nobody tells me these things I just work
没有人告诉我我只是在工作
here
这里
okay I might connect to fied
好吧，我可能会连接到fied
dun start that springdale so if you have
邓开始那个斯普林代尔，所以如果你有
a chance this is an amazing place I go
一个机会，这是我去的地方很棒
here all the time if you have if you're
如果有的话，一直在这里
sad you want something to read that's
难过，你想读一些东西
uplifting it'll warm your hearts we'd
振奋人心的我们
start that spring Rio if your children
如果你的孩子，那年春天开始里约
are restless and you can't get them to
躁动不安，你不能让他们去
sleep start that spring IL if you're
如果你在
uncomfortable having bad dreams keep it
梦bad以求的不舒服
under your pillow the ultimate comfort
在枕头下极致舒适
now some of you are programmers I'm a
现在你们中有些是程序员，我是
programmer sorta I mean in theory right
程序员排序我在理论上是正确的
and the elite among us well of course a
当然我们中间的精英们
shoe a web a web interface so we're
试穿一个网络界面，以便我们
going to use we can also use curl start
要使用我们也可以使用curl start
out spring today over because this far
今天春天结束了，因为到目前为止
more command-line friendly
更命令行友好
isn't that amazing I think there should
我认为应该没有那么神奇
be a telnet interface but nobody listens
成为telnet界面，但没人听
to me on the spring team so so whatever
对我来说，在春季队中
okay that's one option I'm also kind of
好吧，这也是我的一种选择
lazy so we're going to use this we're
懒，所以我们要用这个
going to build a simple domain it's a
要建立一个简单的域，这是一个
micro service called reservation service
微服务称为预订服务
like so can you see that and we are a
像这样，你能看到吗，我们是一个
reservation - service and it's going to
预订-服务，它将
be a web application so I'll build a web
成为网络应用程序，所以我将建立一个网络
application I'm going to use JPA because
应用程序，我将使用JPA，因为
I make poor life decisions
我做出糟糕的生活决定
okay so JPA um I'm going to use spring
好的，所以JPA嗯，我要用spring
data rest repositories to map my my
数据其余存储库以映射我的我的
application so the balance is the life
应用程序，所以平衡就是生命
decision right exactly least I get to my
正确的决定至少我能做到
others pain IVs h2 embedded data in the
其他人则将IVs h2嵌入数据
embedded database for in-memory
用于内存的嵌入式数据库
Hannukah no she's actuator and the
Hannukah不，她是执行器，
remote and I'm not gonna use remote Joe
远程，我将不使用远程乔
I'm gonna eat actually actually um it'll
我要吃的实际上是
come with it um I also have choices
来吧，我也有选择
naturally this is a you know Springs you
自然，这是一个你知道的春天
have choices you can choose if you are
有选择就可以选择
by some fluke of physics stuck in the
被困在
distant past unable to move forward to
遥不可及的过去无法前进
the future which let's face it is just
让我们面对的未来就是
today then you can choose var now me and
今天，那么你可以选择var now me and
you we're all here today in the same
你我们今天都在同一地点
room in 2015 so we're going to choose
房间在2015年，所以我们要选择
jar even though you have a friend doctor
罐子，即使你有一位朋友医生
here who can write travel in time not
在这里谁能及时写旅行
that's true
确实如此
darn it this is ill cheese jazz of
哎呀，这是爵士的不适
course uh this isn't keeping with my
当然，这不符合我的
personal philosophy of make jar not war
做罐子不是战争的个人哲学
now again whatever your choice you know
现在再说一次，无论您知道什么
it if you can choose what I want okay
如果可以选择我想要的就可以
now I'm also going to integrate this
现在我也要整合这个
we're going to choose the config client
我们将选择配置客户端
we'll choose
我们会选择
a Eureka discovery support we're going
我们将提供的尤里卡发现支持
to choose a what else do I need here doc
选择我在这里还需要什么doc
is service
是服务
Oh Redis yeah I need to choose spring
哦，Redis，是的，我需要选择弹簧
boot 1.3 o m5 so I can see the new
启动1.3 o m5，以便我可以看到新的
spring cloud bits that's important stuff
春天的云点很重要
down yeah
没错
I'm going to choose spring cloud stream
我要选择春天的云流
Redis and I'm going to choose Zipkin and
Redis和我将选择Zipkin和
I think that'll do for this and we'll
我想这会做到的，我们会
come back to it a bit okay so this is
回到它还好，所以这是
our first service we're going to stand
我们的第一项服务，我们将立于不败之地
it up and I'm just going to build a
它，我将要建立一个
simple REST API here that's the goal
简单的REST API，这就是目标
here is just a to build something that
这只是建立一个东西
we can play with so I'll get rid of all
我们可以一起玩，所以我会摆脱一切
that hit generate open this up and this
命中产生打开这个
is just spring boot at this point I mean
这只是春天的靴子
I've got some spring cut bits on the
我在刀架上有一些弹簧切块
classpath but what we're going to
类路径，但是我们要做的是
demonstrate here is just a basic spring
展示这里只是一个基本的春天
boot application and there are many
启动应用程序，有很多
great talks on spring boot here so you
关于 spring boot 的精彩演讲，所以您
know I've made this as as big as I can
知道我已经尽力了
get it if you need it bigger you let me
得到它，如果您需要更大，让我
know ok here we go
知道好了，我们走了
so I've got a maven build palm that XML
所以我已经有了一个XML专家。
I'm going to go ahead and comment out a
我将继续进行评论
few things so right now I don't want
我现在不想的几件事
Eureka and the config stuff so we're
尤里卡和配置的东西，所以我们
just going to leave spring cloud stream
刚要离开春天的云流
bits off ok I'm going to build a simple
好的，我要建立一个简单的
REST API so I'll say hello computer
REST API，所以我打个招呼
synchronize there we go you got cached
同步到那里，我们去缓存了
I'm going to place to it what is that
我要放的是那是什么
Eclipse you're using that I'm going to
您正在使用的Eclipse我将要
build a simple domain I'm going to use a
建立一个简单的域，我将使用
reservation entity this is a JP entity
保留实体，这是一个JP实体
it's a it's a nonsensically simple
这是一个毫无意义的简单
domain I don't really want to focus on
我真的不想关注的领域
the domain we just need to have
我们只需要拥有的域名
something to talk to naturally so say
自然要说话的东西
private string reservation name and I'll
私人字串保留名称，我将
say getter and I'll say I want a
说吸气剂，我会说我想要一个
constructor and it's going to have an ID
构造函数，它将有一个ID
so I'll give it a primary key there at
所以我在这里给它一个主键
ID at generated value I'll give it a two
ID为生成值，我给它两个
string method naturally okay I'll give
字符串方法自然可以，我会给
it a constructor for my object-oriented
它是面向对象的构造函数
purposes I'll give it another
目的我再给它
constructor for JPA right so why JP why
JPA的构造函数正确，为什么选择JP为什么
right and that'll do right now I need a
对，现在就要做，我需要一个
way to store that in a database so I'll
将其存储在数据库中的方式，我将
use a repository I'll say interface
使用存储库，我会说接口
reservation repository ok extends JP a
预订存储库还可以扩展JP a
repository now this is just
现在这只是仓库
a repository that'll managed entities of
将管理以下实体的存储库
type reservation whose primary key is a
类型保留，其主键是
type of long it's going to have a custom
长的类型将有一个自定义
finder method so I'll say find by
Finder方法，所以我会说find by
reservation name string RN and a
保留名称字符串RN和一个
naturally I want to expose exposes over
我自然要暴露
the web so I'll use spring data rest
网络，所以我将使用spring数据休息
I'll say rest report a repository rest
我会说休息报告仓库休息
resource I'm going to map this finder
我将要映射此查找器的资源
method also to a web service so I'll say
方法也适用于Web服务，所以我会说
rest resource path equals by name and
其余资源路径按名称等于
I'll map the parameter here to a HTTP
我将参数映射到HTTP
parameter RN okay good so that'll do
参数RN好的，这样就可以了
that should be our first cut we need
那应该是我们需要的第一个切入点
some data so I'll create a simple
一些数据，所以我将创建一个简单的
command line runner and the command line
命令行运行程序和命令行
winner is going to do something very
优胜者将要做的事情非常
very simple it's going to run when the
非常简单，它将在
application starts up and I'll and I'll
应用程序启动，我会，我会
use and inject it repository to to
使用并将其注入到
create some data
创建一些数据
okay so reservation repository here we
好的，所以这里的预订库
are
是
and I'll say arrays but as list a doctor
我会说数组，但要列出医生
rod doctor sire here again all the
棒医生再次在这里ire下
community and then Josh okay split hello
社区，然后乔希好吧，你好
computer splitting the data into a
计算机将数据分割成一个
record and I'll write this into the
记录，我将其写入
database I'll say for each record in
我会说数据库中的每个记录
that and that relist I'm going to say X
那和那个重新列出我要说的X
RR dot save new reservation ok and then
RR点保存新的保留，然后
I'm going to print out the information
我将打印出信息
that I get back from the client so I'll
我从客户那里回来，所以我会
say for each system that out and I'm
说出来的每个系统，我
using Java 8 lambdas by the way how many
顺便说一下使用Java 8 lambda
of you are using Java 8 lambdas or Java
你们中的人正在使用Java 8 lambdas或Java
8 oh ok well Jason a number that's that
8哦，好吧，杰森，那是一个数字
you should be a little high well that's
你应该高一点
Java 8 is pretty pretty sweet my friends
我的朋友，Java 8非常漂亮
you you got to do it the other ones are
你你必须去做，其他的是
also end-of-life save for security
使用寿命也更长，以确保安全
updates so you know give yourself a hug
更新，所以你知道给自己一个拥抱
that eight good stuff okay
那八个好东西好吗
anyway let's run this let's see what we
无论如何，让我们运行这个，让我们看看我们
get we should have a simple REST API
得到我们应该有一个简单的REST API
using hypermedia using spring data rest
使用超媒体使用Spring Data Rest
which of course the good doctors hire so
好的医生当然会雇用哪个
skillfully and usefully demonstrated
熟练而有用地展示
yesterday it failed it failed because
昨天失败了，失败了，因为
it's running on
它正在运行
the same port as another application so
与另一个应用程序相同的端口，因此
I'm gonna go here and I'll curse that
我要去这里，我会诅咒
was intentional right yeah yeah that was
是故意的，是的，是的
some I don't know 80 27 I don't care who
一些我不知道80 27我不在乎谁
cares just go we have something called
随便去吧，我们有一个叫做
Zipkin which is awesome but it's causing
Zipkin很棒，但它正在引起
me pain and heartburn 19 just not yeah
我痛苦和胃灼热19只是不是
right no we can pick it up later
是的，不，我们稍后再取
so reservations let's see what we get no
所以预订让我们看看我们得到了什么
it's 1880 25 s that really setting yeah
是在1880年25年代
sorry okay there we go so now we have
抱歉，好的，我们去了，现在我们有了
some basic data now the goal here is to
一些基本数据，现在的目标是
build a service that takes advantage of
建立利用以下优势的服务
some of these things you're going to
其中一些你要去的东西
need when you move into a distributed
迁移到分布式系统时需要
systems architecture the first thing
系统架构第一件事
you're going to want is centralized
您要集中的
configuration we talked about cloud
我们谈论云的配置
native applications who talked about 12
谈到12的本机应用程序
factor app style configuration the idea
应用程式样式设定的构想
that every application should have
每个应用程序都应该有
external to the binary itself the
在二进制本身之外
configuration that's needed to move it
移动它所需的配置
successfully from one environment to
从一个环境成功地
another passwords host names ports these
另一个密码主机名将这些端口
kinds of locators and credentials that
各种定位器和凭证
stuff doesn't belong in the build and of
东西不属于构建和
course you can use environment variables
当然你可以使用环境变量
or - the arguments or what have you
或-参数或您有什么
spring boot makes it deadly simple but
弹簧靴使它变得非常简单，但
as you start to scale you're going to
当您开始扩展时，您将
need more going to need centralized
需要更多需要集中化
configuration first of all if I want to
首先要配置
change configuration I want to be able
更改我想要的配置
to do so in a single place if I want to
如果我想在一个地方这样做
have passwords I want to be able to do
有我想做的密码
symmetric encryption and decryption from
来自的对称加密和解密
my password file which is after all on
我的密码文件毕竟是
the file system to the application that
应用程序的文件系统
uses that password again you need some
再次使用该密码，您需要一些密码
of the intermediary if I wanna be able
如果我想能够
to change things live while the system
改变生活而系统
is running for example for canary are
例如金丝雀正在运行
sorry for feature flags and these sort
对不起，功能标记之类的
of things again it's nice to have an
再有一件事情很高兴
extra facility in between your
您之间的额外设施
properties and the apps that use them so
属性以及使用它们的应用程序
we're going to turn to the spring cloud
我们将转向春天的云
a config server so start that spring
一个配置服务器，所以从那个春天开始
that IO and I'm going to choose a spring
IO和我要选择弹簧
boot 1/3 om5 and I'll go down here I'm
启动1/3 om5，我会在这里下去
going to say a config server and I'll
要说一个配置服务器，我会
tell it to um I think they'll do just
告诉我，我想他们会做的
due to civilian aid ok and the goal here
由于平民援助还可以，这里的目标
is I'm going to let config server which
我要让配置服务器
is a REST API on top of a git based
是基于git的REST API
repository
资料库
right or a filesystem depository or
权利或文件系统存放处或
subversion supposin as well as
颠覆素和
subversion the idea is that these things
颠覆思想是这些东西
are except for the file system very good
除了文件系统非常好
at auditing and rolling back
在审核和回滚时
configuration changes so if something
配置更改，所以如果有的话
should happen say that dr. sire and I
应该发生说博士。父亲和我
got off stage and then got sloshed to
下台，然后滑向
celebrate the delivery of the most
庆祝最大的交付
amazing talk ever
有史以来令人惊讶的谈话
you don't want us to log into production
您不希望我们登录生产
to make changes without the ability to
没有能力进行更改
record what happened and where and then
记录发生了什么事，在哪里，然后
to rollback right so this gives you that
向右回滚，所以这给你
facility so we're going to configure
工具，所以我们要配置
applique moah plication I'm going to say
我要说的是贴花moah叠
you're a config server like so and I'm
你是一个像这样的配置服务器，我
going to point it to a git repository
将其指向git存储库
which I just happen to have conveniently
我碰巧很方便
laying around on my file system here so
在这里放置我的文件系统
I'm going to say spring cloud config
我要说的是Spring Cloud Config
soar forget your AI equals home forward
腾飞忘记您的AI等于回家
slash desktop forward slash config repo
斜杠桌面正斜杠配置仓库
okay so I've got a git based repository
好，所以我有一个基于git的存储库
on my filesystem there I'm also going to
在我的文件系统上，我还将
tell this application to run on port
告诉此应用程序在端口上运行
8888 okay we should start this up now
8888好，我们现在应该开始
and now the first thing we're going to
现在我们要做的第一件事
do is go back and teach our reservation
要做的就是回去教我们的预订
service how to get its configuration
服务如何获取其配置
information from the config server right
来自配置服务器权限的信息
again we want to act as a client to that
再次，我们想作为一个客户
config server so I will go here and
配置服务器，所以我会去这里，
simply uncomment rather than we add the
只是取消注释，而不是我们添加
spring cloud starter config dependency
Spring Cloud Starter配置依赖项
this is going to need some information
这将需要一些信息
in order to work correctly so I'm going
为了正常工作，所以我要
to tell it first of all that its name it
首先告诉它它的名字
has to identify itself after all is app
毕竟必须是应用程序
is called reservation - service and that
称为预订-服务，
the config server lives on port 80 8 8 8
配置服务器位于端口80 8 8 8
on localhost right I could leave the
在本地主机上，我可以离开
default here but it's nice to know this
默认为此处，但很高兴知道这一点
this information as you can imagine
您可以想象的这些信息
needs to happen before the rest of the
需要发生在其余的
applications configuration is evaluated
评估应用程序配置
it needs to be needs to happen in the
它需要发生在
bootstrap so what I'm going to do is I'm
引导程序，所以我要做的就是
going to rename this property called
将重命名此属性为
application that properties this file
该文件属性的应用程序
I'm going to rename it a bootstrap type
我将其重命名为引导程序类型
properties ok so hello computer refactor
属性还可以，所以你好，计算机重构
that should have worked but whatever
那本来可以用，但是无论如何
boot strap dot properties and that's the
引导带点属性，这就是
only configuration we're gonna have from
我们将拥有的唯一配置
one service to another again the goal
一种服务，另一种服务的目标
here is to write as little as possible
这是写得越少越好
and get the benefit we have to config
并获得我们必须配置的好处
server running here on localhost 8
在本地主机8上运行的服务器
and I'm going to show you what the
我将向您展示
configuration for example for the
例如配置
service that identifies itself as
标识为
reservation service looks like I'm going
预订服务好像我要去
to go to reservation service master and
去预订服务主管和
I can see in this JSON string the is
我可以在这个JSON字符串中看到
what result rather that I have two
结果是我有两个
property files one called reservation
物业档案一叫保留
service type properties which has three
服务类型属性具有三个
properties including a message and then
属性，包括一条消息，然后
have another property file an
有另一个属性文件
application that llamo file that is more
那个llamo文件的应用程序
generic so every micro service will get
通用的，所以每个微服务都会得到
the configuration in application yeah
是的，在应用程序中的配置
Mueller properties only the service that
Mueller只拥有
identifies itself as reservation service
将自己标识为预订服务
will get the properties in this one
将获得这一属性
should there be a conflict as there is
应该有冲突吗
in this case between server type port in
在这种情况下，服务器类型端口在
the reservation service and server type
预订服务和服务器类型
port in application net properties the
应用程序网络属性中的端口
more specific one will win okay so let's
更具体一点的人会赢的，所以让我们
take advantage of this I'm going to use
利用这一点，我将要使用
the message here this key that's in my
这里的消息是我的钥匙
config server it's a REST API sitting in
配置服务器，它是一个REST API
a separate process I'm going to now
我现在要进行一个单独的过程
configure my spring cloud-based micro
配置基于Spring Cloud的Micro
service reservation service to use that
服务预订服务使用
message and we'll demonstrate a few
消息，我们将演示一些
features he's not going to stop unless
他不会停止的功能，除非
you ask a question but you should ask
你问一个问题，但你应该问
questions if you happen class say you
问题，如果你上课说你
know control he might go down at the end
知道控制权他可能最终会失败
he's going to need a little bit of help
他需要一点帮助
at the end learning this by the way if
最后通过以下方式学习
anybody is a student of the cloud native
任何人都是云原生的学生
thing and you're not too precious about
事情，你不是很珍贵
it this is really I think of it as a
这真的是我认为的
generalization of environment variables
环境变量的概括
so you could just you know easily
这样你就可以轻松知道
translate that
翻译那个
so environment variables great they work
所以环境变量很棒
you know with UNIX processes this is
您知道在UNIX进程中这是
just kind of extending it a spring
只是把它延长了一个春天
already has this thing called an
已经有一个叫做
environment abstraction so we're just
环境抽象，所以我们只是
plugging into that there is a question
插入有一个问题
are we planning on building a UI to sit
我们是否打算建立一个坐式UI
on top of the configuration server
在配置服务器之上
somebody already built it
已经有人建造了
it's called github it's true no
这叫github，是真的，不
seriously there are so many UI is forget
严重的是，有太多的UI忘记了
great answer that i didn't feel like i
我不觉得自己的好答案
should write another one i know i know
应该写另一个我知道我知道的
what he means he means for editing but
他的意思是他意味着要编辑，但
you know that github does that if you
你知道github会做到这一点
don't want to use github you can install
不想使用github可以安装
it you know get lab i've got lots of
你知道我要去实验室吗
clients doing that so it's a great tool
客户这样做是一个很好的工具
George
乔治
we're going to talk about how you change
我们将谈论你如何改变
different environments using the
使用不同的环境
conflict server you could quickly show
您可以快速显示的冲突服务器
that actually he made a mistake there
他实际上在那里犯了一个错误
because he did Master did you see that
因为他做师父，你看到了吗
master on the URL that's actually the
掌握实际上是
name of a spring profile so he could
弹簧轮廓的名称，以便他可以
have put you a a you know you a as a
把你放了，你知道你是一个
profile name test as a profile name it's
配置文件名称测试作为配置文件名称
another
另一个
yeah well it's it's it that then you
是的，那就是你
need an environment variable right so
需要一个环境变量，所以
you need something that's going to
你需要一些东西
change within each one so what I would
改变每个人，所以我会
do is I would push the Cloud Foundry was
我要做的就是推Cloud Foundry
you know M spring cloud profiles active
你知道M春季云资料活跃
equals you at UA and then that would
在UA等于您，然后
pick up the config from the right
从右边拿起配置
profile let's go we gotta go I'm sorry
个人资料让我们走吧，我们得走了，对不起
holder question we want the questions
持有人问题，我们要的问题
but let's do it at the end because we
但让我们在最后做，因为我们
have later started I just want but the
后来开始，我只是想要但是
goal here is for you to leave with your
这里的目标是让您随身携带
eyes tearing your hair and fire yeah
眼睛在撕扯你的头发，着火了
this is not a gentle introduction to see
这不是一个温和的介绍
the kitchen sink I want you understand
我想让你知道的厨房水槽
what the destination is once you
你一旦到达目的地
understand that then you can go to the
了解，那么你可以去
amazing deep dives later on with the
之后，您可以进行惊人的深潜
good doctor sire and Mark Fisher oh yeah
好医生父亲和马克·费舍尔哦，是的
that's worth mentioning
值得一提
so yeah yes G but we haven't we haven't
所以，是的，G，但我们没有，我们没有
hit any of that stuff yet no I'll open
打任何东西，但不，我打开
it the deep dives are later this is
深潜是后来这是
where this is 101 you got to see what
这是101的地方
the destination is and you're gonna want
目的地是，而你想要
to go there it's good so I have this
去那里很好，所以我有这个
message value I have this little value
消息值，我有这个小值
that I stood up as a rest service
我站起来作为休息服务
I created this rest service like so I
我像这样创建了这项休息服务
said message rest controller I injected
说我注入的消息休息控制器
the message from the property file on
来自属性文件的消息在
the config service and I'm just a stood
配置服务，我只是站着
up an endpoint that will respond to a
端点将响应
forward slash message I want to change
我要更改的正斜杠消息
this message this is a useless message
这是一条无用的消息
you're not the world here you're better
你不是这里的世界，你更好
you're spring one so we're going to go
你是一个春天，所以我们要去
to the file system here we're going to
到这里的文件系统，我们将
go to my desktop desktop CD config
转到我的桌面桌面CD配置
service or config repo and I have files
服务或配置库，我有文件
in there so I'm going to say Joe
在那儿，我要说乔
reservation service type properties and
预订服务类型属性和
I'm going to change this file say hello
我要更改此文件打个招呼
spring one command X okay I'm going to
发出一个命令X好，我要去
say git commit minus a minus
说git commit减减号
Yolo get status okay
Yolo的状态还可以
so I've changed it I've got little
所以我改变了，我几乎没有
droppings from my ID there but that's
从我的身份证那里掉下来，但这就是
not the actual files so there we are we
不是实际的文件，所以我们就在这里
made the change if I go to the config
如果我转到配置进行了更改
server itself the new value is
服务器本身的新价值是
immediately visible right but my old
马上可见，但我的老
service which injects that value is not
注入价值的服务不是
yet updated to reflect that so one way
尚未更新以反映这一点
to update it is to trigger a refresh
更新它是触发刷新
that's what that annotation is at
这就是注释所在
refresh I can do this many different
刷新我可以做很多不同的事情
ways one is just to use the local
一种方法是只使用本地
actuator endpoint called refresh on the
执行器端点称为刷新
node itself another way is to use a
节点本身的另一种方法是使用
spring cloud MPP bus to connect
春云MPP总线连接
different nodes by a rabid em cube
狂热的em多维数据集可实现不同的节点
either way the effect is that you're
无论哪种方式，效果是
telling the app instance to find all the
告诉应用实例查找所有
beans that have this annotation refresh
具有此批注的bean刷新
scope and to recreate the beans in situ
范围和原位重新创建bean
thus reevaluating the property from the
因此，从
config server so let's do that okay
配置服务器，让我们这样做吧
curl - D that's empty post basically
curl-D基本上是空的帖子
localhost 8004 word slash refresh and
本地主机8004斜杠刷新和
then I get a sad face what is it was
然后我很难过，那是什么
that reaffirm Lord that there was a t25
重申主耶稣说过
wasn't it no but I threw that away cuz
不是吗，但我把那个扔掉了
it away because you're now in the config
它消失了，因为您现在在配置中
server yeah um did I just forget to add
服务器是的，我只是忘记添加了
the actuator yeah yeah that's what you
执行器是的，那是你
did okay awkward spring yeah he was
春天好不好意思，他当时
right was wrong as usual I think there
像往常一样，我认为那是对的
was a time when he gave this demo like
那个时候他给这个演示像
in spring cloud 1.0.0 when it would have
在春季云1.0.0中
been but some somebody said white excuse
曾经但是有人说白人借口
me why do we need to activate it for
我为什么我们需要激活它
every content client so we pulled it out
每个内容客户，所以我们将其淘汰
that would explain it okay awkward so
那会解释它好尴尬，所以
let's do this one more time huh take two
让我们再做一次，花两个
okay updated nope haha umm well it does
好的，更新了，不，哈哈，嗯，很好
it have actuator endpoint
它具有执行器端点
have mappings yeah you should order to
有映射，是的，您应该订购
say it mappings nah right so there's
说它映射不对，所以有
something else going on that this is the
还有其他事情，这是
reservation that maybe started to eat
可能开始吃饭的预订
yeah mavin re-import now's the time not
是的，现在是时候重新导入
to screw around mr. application there it
拧紧先生。在那里申请
is so now is there a refresh that ok
现在是这样，可以刷新吗
let's go here again take three third
让我们再去这里三分之三
time is the charm
时间就是魅力
we hope good so instant did you say it
我们希望很好，所以你立刻说了
tells you that he changed the message
告诉你他改变了消息
yeah message is blink there we go if
是的消息是眨眼，如果
you're paying attention you okay
你在注意你没事
you can applause that's okay I deserve
你可以鼓掌，我应该得到的
it I do I do actually like I said he
我确实做到了，就像我说他
wrote the code I'm just dancing on stage
写了我在舞台上跳舞的代码
so I'm moving on
所以我继续
that's one pattern a centralized
这是集中式的一种模式
configuration a second pattern when you
当您配置第二种模式
move to a spring application we move to
移至我们将移至的Spring应用程序
a cloud application you're going to have
您将拥有的云应用程序
lots of lots of instances that live and
大量存在的实例
die their ephemeral as capacity dictates
因能力要求而短暂逝世
right as capacity demands so you want
根据容量需求而定
the ability to be decoupled from host
与主机分离的能力
names and ports we talked about that and
我们讨论过的名称和端口，以及
yesterday's epic keynote up what this
昨天的史诗般的主题演讲
implies is I cannot rely on DNS I need
暗示我不能依靠我需要的DNS
something to give me a bit of a
有些东西给我一点
decoupling the way you do that is to use
去耦你的方式就是使用
a service registry it's a bit of a
服务注册表有点
phonebook it's a way of saying I want to
电话簿是我想说的一种方式
talk to that service over there and I
与那边的服务部门交谈，我
know the name but I don't know the host
知道名字，但我不知道主持人
important the other benefit of this is
重要的另一个好处是
that I can also do client-side load
我也可以做客户端负载
balancing I no longer need to rely on
平衡我不再需要依靠
DNS to know what kind of load dancing
DNS知道什么样的负载跳舞
I'm supposed to do across services so
我应该跨服务来做
I'm going to go back to startup spring
我要回到春天开始
that I own and I'm going to build or
我拥有的，我将要建立或
stand up a Eureka registry using Eureka
使用Eureka站起Eureka注册表
server here it's gonna be a config
服务器在这里它将是一个配置
client as well so again what we're doing
客户也是如此，我们在做什么
is we're standing up a service it
是我们要站起来服务吗
shouldn't I wouldn't do this normally
我不应该正常做吗
there's you can stand up Eureka easily
您可以轻松地站起尤里卡
like this but then you have to set up in
这样，但您必须在
a highly available way you're going to
一种高度可用的方式
normally have this running somewhere not
通常在没有地方运行
going to do it many times from here like
要从这里做很多次
I am or you might use sorry you might
我是，或者您可能会后悔，您可能会
use
采用
Cloud Foundry to do it yeah the Cloud
Cloud Foundry做到这一点，云
Foundry has a very good service red
铸造厂有很好的服务红
sheet you might also use and I don't
您可能还会使用的床单，但我不
know zookeeper oh one of those other
认识动物园管理员哦，其中一个
things right yeah yeah Spencer's giving
没错，是Spencer的付出
a talk this afternoon I think or is it
我想是今天下午的一次演讲
tomorrow tomorrow about all the new
明天明天关于所有新
stuff in spring cloud so if you're if
春天的云中的东西，所以如果你是
you've used 1.0 and you want to know
您使用过1.0，并且想知道
what's in 1.1 then
那么1.1中有什么
Spencer's getting a talk tomorrow about
斯宾塞明天要谈
that I'll be there also that will
我也会在那里
include the new service discovery
包括新服务发现
implementations a console Cloud Foundry
实现控制台Cloud Foundry
lattice generate Eureka server open a no
点阵生成Eureka服务器打开一个否
computer here we can server open this up
电脑在这里，我们可以服务器打开它
same triggers before I need to connect
我需要连接之前的相同触发器
it to the config server and to the
它到配置服务器和
Eureka and it's going to be a it has to
尤里卡，这将是一个必须
identify itself so I'll copy this
标识自己，所以我将其复制
bootstrapped up properties here's
引导属性在这里
application dot properties I'm going to
我要去的应用程序点属性
paste in here
贴在这里
bootstrap top properties and we're going
引导顶级属性，我们要
to say this is going to be named eureka
说这将被命名为尤里卡
service it is a Eureka service and so I
服务是尤里卡服务，所以我
have to configure to such I'll say at
必须配置为这样，我会在
enable you week a server and that should
使您每周拥有一台服务器，应该
do so I'm going to start it up and it'll
这样做，我将启动它，它将
come up to on port 87-61 because that's
到达端口87-61，因为那是
what we have in the config server
我们在配置服务器中拥有的
specified for it to do so there's this
指定这样做，有这个
this is the spring Eureka you know this
这是春天的尤里卡，你知道这个
is on this is based on Netflix is Eureka
在此基于Netflix是Eureka
say I'm the same basic UI you saw last
说我是上次看到的相同的基本用户界面
night in a demo but that was the Cloud
演示中的一个晚上，但这就是云
Foundry skinning for this so this is
铸造蒙皮，所以这是
running locally and that was running
在本地运行，并且正在运行
into our foundry and that one was much
进入我们的铸造厂，那是很多
more usable for a UI yeah and it's a
对于UI更有用，是的
nice little area it's ajaxy so it it
漂亮的小区域，它是ajaxy这样的
responds when things change so the goal
当事情改变时做出回应，因此目标
here is to get services to show up here
这是让服务显示在这里
right this is a phone book nothing is
对，这是电话本，什么都不是
gonna be able to find each other if they
如果他们能够找到对方
can't they're not registered here so
他们不能不在这里注册吗
let's go back to our can resume ssin
让我们回到可以恢复的状态
service by the way oh remember let's
服务的方式哦，记住我们
talk about in you know the highly
谈谈你知道的高度
available mode this is a eureka barfing
可用的模式，这是尤里卡的推手
all over the console saying where's my
整个控制台都说我在哪里
peer where's my where's another node for
同伴在哪里，我的另一个节点在哪里
replication and it can't find one so
复制，它找不到一个
it's it's throwing up its hands and
是它举起了手，
disgust sheer disgust it'll work but
令人反感，它会起作用，但
this is a reminder that you should
这提醒您，您应该
always configure this in a highly
始终在高度配置中
available fashion so one instance does
可用的时尚，所以一个实例
not a highly available
不是高度可用
we constancy or deployment meek okay we
我们保持不变或部署温顺，好吧，我们
tried to switch that off but it's
试图将其关闭，但这是
impossible yeah
是不可能的
it really isn't McGarrett I really won't
真的不是麦加雷特，我真的不会
need to see that yeah so we've got that
需要看到是的，所以我们有
now let's go back to the reservation
现在让我们回到预订
service and bring in the support for
服务并带来对
talking to the registry now remember we
现在与注册表进行对话，请记住我们
have an abstraction here called the
在这里有一个抽象称为
discovery client abstraction it's common
发现客户端抽象很常见
to all of these different service
所有这些不同的服务
registry implementations but the things
注册表实现，但事情
you're going to do with the discovery
您将与发现相关
client with the with the service
客户与服务
registries at the very minimum you're
至少您是
going to ask questions of it you can ask
要问的问题你可以问
where does this service live is it
该服务住在哪里？
available how do I talk to it sometimes
有时我该如何交谈
you may also have to write to it you may
您可能还必须写信给您
have to say if you need me I'm here
必须说如果您需要我，我在这里
right that's optional so for example
对，这是可选的，例如
Cloud Foundry which is or latus these
这些是Cloud Foundry还是latus这些
are both platforms they already know
是他们已经知道的两个平台
where the service has been stood up you
服务站在那里
don't need to tell it right till our
直到我们讲完才告诉
discovery client implementations are
发现客户端实现是
read-only in that case but naturally a
在这种情况下为只读，但自然
Eureka console zookeeper they need a
尤里卡控制台动物园管理员，他们需要一个
little bit more hand-holding so in that
多一点点的手持
case they both register and read from it
他们都注册并从中读取的情况
okay so I've got that up and running if
好的，所以我已经启动并运行了
I go to here there you see there's our
我去这里，你看到那里是我们的
service registered in the Eco registry
在生态注册表中注册的服务
it's there's one instance it's running
它正在运行一个实例
it's up and so on this host name I now
已经启动，依此类推，我现在在此主机名上
need to write a client I want to build
需要写一个我想建立的客户
our first client something to talk to it
我们的第一个客户有话要说
so reservation service reservation
所以预订服务预订
client ok doc what do we need you we
客户确定文档我们需要什么我们
good discovery Eureka a config client
很好的发现Eureka一个配置客户端
you are going to do don't see the
你要做的看不到
security because I don't think it's
安全，因为我不认为这是
gonna work sorry don't do the security
要工作对不起不要做安全
no ok we won't bother um these are
不，我们不会打扰这些
milestones friends you guys happen
你们发生的里程碑朋友
you're gonna do is it can eventually oh
你会做的是最终可以哦
yes thank you finding the Redis stream
是的，谢谢您发现Redis流
yeah mark and I are doing a talk on
是的，马克，我正在谈
spring clouds rain this afternoon
春天的云今天下午下雨
looking data killing Emily so we'll see
寻找杀死Emily的数据，所以我们将看到
it really quickly down anything else I'm
它真的很快使我失去了其他任何东西
going shopping it's always nice to have
去购物总是很高兴
everything you want in one basket but
您想要的所有东西都放在一个篮子里
okay here we go reservation clients open
好吧，我们去预订客户。
now the goal here we're going to build
现在我们要建立的目标
an application that talks toward to our
与我们对话的应用程序
micro service and it's going to discover
微服务，它将发现
the micro service through the registry
通过注册表进行微服务
this is going to be a client first of
这将是第一个客户
all but it's also going to be in an edge
所有，但也将处于边缘
service something that will sit at the
服务的东西会坐在
edge of your data center and be exposed
数据中心的边缘并暴露在外
to other
到其他
services right so when I another things
服务很好，所以当我另一件事
like iPads and iPhones and you know
像iPad和iPhone，你知道
html5 browsers and so on so we're going
html5浏览器等等，所以我们要
to build an API you know what we don't
建立一个API，你知道我们不知道
what we want to do is first connect this
我们想要做的是首先连接这个
to the registry we wanted to get the
到我们想要获得的注册表
configuration so I'll say enable
配置，所以我说启用
discovery client just as we did before
像以前一样发现客户
and I'll change the resources stuff or
然后我将更改资源内容或
application up properties into
将属性应用到
bootstrapped up properties rename it so
引导属性重命名，以便
it'll be called reservation client now I
我现在叫预约客户
want to build a client that talks to
想要建立一个与之交谈的客户
these other services the reason you do
这些其他服务的原因
this is because you have different kinds
这是因为你有不同的种类
of actual clients that will talk to
与之交谈的实际客户
these mid tier services it's nice to
这些中端服务很高兴
have an intermediary and edge service
有中介和边缘服务
like this that sits between your iPhones
像这样位于您的iPhone之间
or iPads and so on and the mid tier
或iPad等以及中端产品
services like our reservation service
像我们的预订服务这样的服务
Netflix does this Netflix have 600
Netflix做到这一点Netflix有600
different micro services they don't want
他们不想要的不同的微服务
to have to update each micro service
必须更新每个微服务
whatever a new client with protocol
不管有协议的新客户
specific requirements or security
特定要求或安全性
requirements or API granularity
要求或API粒度
requirements are introduced like if
引入需求就像
there's new iPad they don't want to have
他们不想拥有新的iPad
to update each of those 600 micro
更新这600个微
services so instead they build something
服务，所以他们建立了一些东西
in the middle and this is called an edge
在中间，这称为边缘
service there's a couple of different
服务有几个不同的地方
kinds of edge services one is a micro
各种边缘服务之一是微服务
proxy imagine for example an html5
代理想象例如一个html5
application html5 has cross-origin
应用程序html5具有跨域
request forgery limitations you can't
要求您不能伪造的限制
make requests that run afoul of this
提出与此违背的要求
security model so it has to be the same
安全模型，因此必须相同
host same domain sure you could go to
托管同一域，请确定您可以访问
each one of those 600 micro services and
这600项微服务中的每一项和
add a policy that permits cross-origin
添加允许跨域的策略
requests to those services but that
对这些服务的要求，但那
would be tedious and require a crazy
会很乏味并且需要疯狂
amount of work right especially
正确的工作量
considering it's just one actual client
认为这只是一个实际的客户
so it's instead better to have a proxy
所以最好有一个代理
that sits in between we're going to use
位于我们要使用的中间
a dual now if you are up on your
如果您正在忙着，现在双打
Ghostbusters mythology you know that Zoo
捉鬼敢死队神话你知道动物园
is the gatekeeper okay isn't that
看门人好吗，不是吗
adorable so cute that's the monster that
很可爱，很可爱
guards the underworld okay send your
守护黑社会好吧，把你的
fridge yeah in a few days in my fridge
在冰箱里放几天冰箱
so so we're going to use a table Zul
因此，我们将使用表Zul
proxy and that may be enough all this is
代理，这可能就足够了
going to do is it's going to stand up a
要做的是站起来
proxy that connects to the service
连接到服务的代理
registry and forwards requests to the
注册表并将请求转发给
services available in that registry so
该注册表中可用的服务，因此
in our case let's see what happens if I
在我们的情况下，让我们看看如果我
go to to demo application I just run it
去演示应用程序，我只是运行它
we should see something this might be
我们应该看到一些可能是
enough again if you're using html5 and
如果您使用的是html5和
you've got a you've got this requirement
你有一个你有这个要求
add this annotation figure out why it
添加此注释找出原因
blew up what did i do what did I do
炸毁了我做了什么我做了什么
conditional oh did I not up see we
有条件的哦，我没有看到我们吗
didn't do the Zul starter we didn't
没有做我们没有的祖尔首发
write awkward I did I here I thought you
写尴尬我在这里吗我以为你
didn't and I thought maybe he did didn't
没有，我想也许他没有
know you didn't I didn't say you click
知道你不是我不是说你点击
it in the finish vizor awkward all right
它在完成vizor尴尬的所有权利
okay so if you have an html5 application
好的，如果您有html5应用程序
maybe all you need to do is forward
也许你需要做的就是前进
request from the client to the mid-tier
客户到中间层的请求
services you add ssl you add um some
您添加ssl的服务您添加了一些
sort of security maybe HTTP basic or
某种安全性，例如HTTP基本或
OAuth or something and then you're done
OAuth之类的，然后就完成了
maybe that's enough maybe you don't mind
也许就足够了，也许你不介意
making multiple chatty requests from the
从
client the html5 browser to these
客户端html5浏览器
mid-tier services and you're not really
中层服务，而您并不是真的
trying to optimize for bandwidth because
尝试优化带宽，因为
it's at this time desktop 5 browser or
目前是台式机5浏览器或
whatever you know so I can go here on
随便你，我就可以继续
say 80 50 reservation service forward
说80 50预订服务转发
slash reservations and it'll sort of not
大刀阔斧的保留，它不会
work what happened now Oh Zipkin
工作现在发生了什么事哦Zipkin
Adrian so we're going to reintroduce
阿德里安，所以我们要重新介绍
this later in the meantime I'm going to
在此期间的稍后，我要
curse under my breath you can't hear
在我的呼吸下诅咒你听不到
that right
那个权利
what it's going to do is it's going to
它要做的是
stand up a proxy that will forward all
站起来将转发所有的代理
requests to the service that's specified
对指定服务的请求
here in the context path right so 8050
这里在上下文路径中，所以8050
forward slash reservation service for
的斜线预订服务
slash reservations there we go
大刀阔斧的保留，我们去了
cheese so there's the data coming from
奶酪，所以数据来自
the reservation service on another on
预订服务在另一个
another node right so I'm insert a link
另一个节点正确，所以我插入一个链接
so I look at the links look at HSN
所以我看链接看HSN
innings sorry
对不起
8050 right yeah 8050 versus 8,000 and
8050对8050对8,000和
notice that the context path isn't there
注意上下文路径不存在
so this is the actual surface the
所以这是实际的表面
original one but it's registered in the
原始的，但已在
service registry under the name
名称下的服务注册表
reservation service so any request that
预订服务，因此任何要求
goes to four slash reservation services
去四个斜线预订服务
for slash gets forwarded naturally to
斜线自然地转发给
the service in the registry maybe that's
注册表中的服务可能就是
enough you know but that would be a
足够你知道，但这将是一个
lousy demo and we can tree stop here so
糟糕的演示，我们可以在这里停下来
it's not enough obviously another use
显然这还不够用
case for an edge service is a api
边缘服务的情况是一个api
gateway right this is a micro proxy but
网关，这是一个微型代理，但是
maybe I want to do API translation I
也许我想做API翻译
want to take the payloads that are being
想要获取正在被
respond returned from the client and
从客户端返回的响应和
transform them maybe give a client
转变他们也许给客户
specific payload that is more
特定的有效载荷
appropriate or you know whatever your
合适的，或者你知道你的任何事情
use case is so I'm going to build as
用例是，所以我将构建为
bill goda in the room what counts a
房间里的比尔·戈达
billow is asking me last night about
昨晚海浪问我
what this problem there you go so we're
你会遇到什么问题，所以我们
going to build a a service or another
将要建立一个服务或其他
rest control controller that will talk
会说话的休息控制控制器
to our reservation service but it's
到我们的预订服务，但这是
going to do some basic translation
要做一些基本的翻译
advice on the client now right yeah
现在就向客户提供建议吧
reservation client and it's going to
预订客户端，它将
called reservation api gateway gateway
称为保留api网关的网关
rest controller i am nothing if not
休息控制器我什么都不是
succinct we need a factory or something
简而言之，我们需要工厂或其他东西
right yeah so I'll say reservation know
是的，所以我会说预订知道
what I'm going to say is I want to
我要说的是我想
inject a rest template because I want to
注入一个休息模板，因为我想
create a rest service that returns the
创建一个休息服务，返回
reservation names I don't return all the
保留名称我不会全部退还
reservation data itself just the names
预订数据本身只是名称
from that collection of reservation
从那个预订集合中
objects I'm going to map from
我要从中映射的对象
reservation to the reservation name in
保留到保留名称中
just a simple nonsensically trivial
只是一个简单的，毫无意义的琐碎
mapping but it's it's a useful exercise
映射，但这是一个有用的练习
okay so when I do this I'm going to use
好的，所以当我这样做时，我将使用
the injected rest template right just
注入的休息模板就在
need to be load downs yeah oh yeah so
需要减负，是的，所以
that's load I'm going to look I'm gonna
这是我要看的负载
make it load dance and what that's going
让它开始跳舞，这是怎么回事
to do is it's going to let me make calls
要做的就是让我打电话
and have them load down automatically by
并让它们自动加载
a component called ribbon and we'll talk
一个称为功能区的组件，我们将讨论
about that in a second so I'm going to
关于这一点，所以我要
say this stress template that exchange
说这个压力模板
HTTP colon forward slash reservation -
HTTP冒号正斜杠保留-
service forward slash reservation so
服务正斜杠保留，所以
again this is not DNS this is the
再次，这不是DNS，这是
service ID as it was registered in
注册的服务ID
Eureka like apprised if it was it just
尤里卡喜欢被告知是否仅仅是
to underline that I mean I'd be
强调我的意思是我会
surprised at this point if there was any
在这一点上是否感到惊讶
other rest template in the context but
上下文中的其他休息模板，但
what he just did was add at load balance
他刚才所做的就是增加负载平衡
which is an @ qualifier person over at
这是@的合格者
Spring 2.5 feature isn't two point five
Spring 2.5功能不是两点五
right now so we're saying we want a rest
现在我们要说要休息
template but not any old rest I'm late
模板，但没有任何我迟到的旧休息
we want the one that's load balanced
我们想要一个负载均衡的
it's it's documentation if nothing else
这是文件，如果没有别的
I don't think ever hurt so we're gonna
我认为永远不会受伤，所以我们要
we're going to tell the rest template to
我们将告诉其余模板
make this request and to pick from all
提出此要求并从所有人中挑选
the registered instances one node to
一个节点的注册实例
make the request - this is going to be
发出请求-这将是
done by something called ribbon which is
由所谓的功能区完成
a software-defined load balancer it's
一个软件定义的负载均衡器
going to in software in the client pick
在客户端选择软件
the instance and then route the request
实例，然后路由请求
by default you'll get round-robin load
默认情况下，您将获得循环加载
balancing but I might want something
平衡，但我可能想要一些东西
like you know multi-tenancy I might want
就像你知道我可能想要多租户
a availability zone awareness you know I
你知道我对可用区的认识
might whatever that use cases I want the
可能无论我想要什么用例
ability to evolve and make that decision
做出决定的能力
in the client it's much easier to do so
在客户中，这样做更容易
then at your Big Five router name for
然后以您的五大路由器名称
example play tennis a slip to big poster
例如打网球到大海报
child yep take the least late and read
是的，孩子要花最少的时间阅读
yeah exactly if you have a six service
是的，如果您有六项服务
behind the behind the load bouncer and
在负载弹跳器后面和
you know you can't tell right doesn't
你知道你不能说对不对
way to ask that question now so having
现在问这个问题的方式
that logic in the client is a very very
客户端中的逻辑是非常非常
powerful thing so I need to tell the
强大的东西，所以我需要告诉
rest template that I want a list of the
我想要列表的其余模板
hypermedia data that's coming from the
来自
reservation service I'm going to create
我将要创建的预订服务
a client-side DTO just to store the data
客户端DTO仅用于存储数据
so private long id private string
所以私人长ID私人字符串
reservation name now looks surprisingly
预订名称现在看起来令人惊讶
like the server side
像服务器端
one right yes very very true what else
一种权利是非常非常真实还有什么
only because you've got a really simple
只是因为你有一个非常简单的
domain right yeah normally it would be
域权，是的，通常是
probably a bit different non sensibly
可能有点不合情理
trivial the reason I want to client-side
琐碎我要客户端的原因
detail is because in theory and again
细节是因为从理论上讲
this is just a theory nobody's ever
这只是一个没人能说的理论
proven to my satisfaction that it
令我满意的是
actually happens or that it will happen
实际发生或将要发生
to somebody who sane but in theory the
对理智的人，但理论上
client and the service could the service
客户和服务可以提供服务
could be written in some other
可以用其他方式写
technology besides a spring in Java now
Java之外的新技术
that's a theory it's not actually going
这是理论，实际上并没有
to happen but if it does then you want
发生，但如果发生，那么您想要
to be decoupled from the types on the
与类型分离
class map in the service right so
服务中的类图正确
client-side proxy is what we can use to
客户端代理是我们可以用来
map okay now I'm going to spit I'm going
地图好了，现在我要吐了
to tell the rest template that I want
告诉我想要的其余模板
exactly that result I'm gonna say
我要说的正是这个结果
parametrized type reference of resources
资源的参数化类型引用
this is the spring hypermedia you know
这是你知道的春季超媒体
envelope type from our REST API and it's
REST API中的信封类型，它是
a common type so we don't have any
普通类型，所以我们没有任何类型
hesitation in adding it okay I'm going
犹豫添加它，好吧，我要去
to use resources like this and or not
使用这种资源与否
try again there we are just took a
再试一次，我们只是采取了
second didn't it
第二个不是吗
you're alright maven you're alright now
你是行家，现在还行
it's important it's now appropriate to
重要的是现在适合
spend a minute minute and reflect upon
花一分钟时间思考
the fact that Java doesn't that really
Java并非真的如此
doesn't really type so it has what it
并不是真正的打字，所以它有它
calls charitably a type system but the
慈善地称为类型系统，但
type system is kind of broken with
类型系统与
respect to generics the generics aren't
关于泛型泛型不是
reified that is at one time there's no
重申那是一次没有
way to ask an instance variable with a
用一个问实例变量的方法
generic parameter what it's instance
通用参数是什么实例
type is a collection of T what is T that
type是T的集合T是什么
information is lost at runtime thanks to
由于运行时信息丢失
type erasure you can capture that by
键入擦除可以捕获
having a subclass you can say class X
有一个子类，你可以说X类
extends ArrayList for example string
扩展ArrayList例如字符串
like that and then you say list of
这样，然后您说出
string x equals new X and then one time
字符串x等于新X，然后一次
if I ask using reflection what it's type
如果我问使用反射它是什么类型
is it'll tell me its string because I've
它会告诉我它的字符串，因为我已经
baked it into this hierarchy here but if
在这里把它烤成这个层次
I had just a regular ArrayList that
我只有一个常规的ArrayList
would not work so what we're going to
将无法正常工作，所以我们要
use is a type token pattern to create an
使用是一种类型标记模式来创建
anonymous subclass which captures that
捕获该内容的匿名子类
generic information that's what this is
这就是一般信息
this doesn't compile if I admit that
如果我承认，这不会编译
okay how many people use that already
好吧已有多少人使用过
it's just a spring web feature right
这只是一个春季网络功能
nothing
没有
I'm a fan nothing all that new about it
我是粉丝，没什么新鲜事
it's pretty alright as soon as we have
我们一拥有就可以了
to deal with generics an arrest template
处理仿制药的逮捕模板
we had to have that yeah so there we go
我们必须拥有那个，所以我们去了
so I'm going to pass that little PT re
所以我要通过那个小PT
into this and that'll tell the rest Jim
到这，然后告诉其余的吉姆
but to give me a a payload that I can
但是给我一个我可以的有效载荷
use here we go and now I can I can
使用这里我们去，现在我可以
iterate or I can return the data I'm
迭代，否则我可以返回我的数据
going to say return response entity dot
要说返回响应实体点
get body hold your breath get collection
保持呼吸屏息
stream map reservation get hey doc
流图预订获取嘿文档
collect collect tours not to list okay
收集收集旅行团不要列出
there we are so now I've got this now
我们在那里，所以我现在有了这个
when do we usually wrap up on now and a
我们通常什么时候总结一下
half dozen it's a twelve oh good so good
半打是十二点哦，太好了
look at the group of time okay so now
看看那组时间好吧，现在
I've got a rest service that's gonna
我有休息服务
return a collection of names and I'm
返回一个名字集合，我
going to map that to an endpoint here
要将其映射到此处的端点
forward slash names like so and this is
像这样的正斜杠名称，这是
going to be a rest controller that are
将成为一个休息控制器
mapped to two four slash reservation so
映射到两个四个斜杠保留，所以
this is the client side this is the edge
这是客户端这是优势
service that's talking to the mid-tier
与中间层对话的服务
service that's in the registry and it's
在注册表中的服务
going to turn just a subset of the data
将仅转存一部分数据
there so we start that and we should be
在那里，所以我们开始，我们应该
able to verify that that works okay okay
能够验证是否可以正常运行
here we go this is the micro proxy now
这里我们去，这是现在的微型代理
I'm going to say reservations forward
我要说预订
slash names there's the data okay so we
斜杠名称有数据就可以了，所以我们
have the data just as a collection of
将数据作为
JSON strings not actual JSON objects so
JSON字符串不是实际的JSON对象，因此
that works that's okay we're able to
可以的，我们可以
read the data but what if I want to make
读取数据，但是如果我想做
changes I want to write to the data we
我要写入数据的更改
know we have a distributive system right
知道我们有分配系统的权利
you want to do state synchronization and
你想做状态同步和
some people say all too quickly I think
有些人说得太快了
let's just be clear here that we could
让我们在这里清楚一点，我们可以
use the distributed transactions we can
使用分布式交易，我们可以
use JTA that's no way to run a railroad
使用无法运行铁路的JTA
friends that's a terrible idea a
朋友，这是一个可怕的主意
terrible idea now spring so are you
可怕的想法现在春天了，你也是
gonna what you can do it what are you
你会怎么做
gonna do instead well we're gonna use
会做得更好，我们将使用
messaging I want to spend a second on
我想花一秒钟的消息
that
那
JT anything though because see we it's a
JT什么都可以，因为看到我们这是一个
checkbox and I really want to
复选框，我真的很想
courage people from moving to a
鼓励人们从转移到
distributed world and then bringing the
分散的世界，然后带来
house down with distributed transactions
分散交易
spring boot readily supports JT and
弹簧靴很容易支持JT和
supports distributed transactions
支持分布式交易
without that vente code was written by
没有那个文库代码是由
Adam there's some idiom idiot some idiot
亚当有一些白痴一些白痴
wrote this code and I don't approve of
写下了这段代码，我不同意
what he has done now uh why okay I know
他现在做了什么，为什么我知道
what I'm talking about don't use it just
我在说什么不要只是使用它
you don't want JT a you know once you
你不想JT一个，一旦你知道
know how sausage and distributed
知道如何香肠和分配
transactions are made well I might still
交易做得很好，我可能还会
have the sausage anyway anyway so let's
反正还是有香肠所以让我们
use messaging right oh I know yeah it's
正确使用消息，哦，我知道，是的
like CQRS or something yeah exactly what
像CQRS之类的东西
optimized for consistent rights I want
针对我想要的一致权利进行了优化
speed in my rights but I want to make
加快我的权利，但我想
sure that they eventually get written so
确保他们最终被写成这样
I want eventual consistency so we read
我想要最终的一致性，所以我们阅读
using HTTP right right with what we've
正确使用HTTP
done that and then we're going to write
做到了，然后我们要写
using a post that forwards to a message
使用转发到邮件的帖子
right so that applies messaging and a
正确，以便应用消息传递和
new feature in spring card 1.1 or
Spring Card 1.1的新功能或
Brixton or what's that it's the right
布里克斯顿或什么是正确的
name X to necessarily strain the release
名称X必然会释放
train a new feature in the new version
在新版本中训练新功能
of spring cloud is that we have the
春天的云是我们有
concept of a release train another new
发布火车的概念另一个新
feature in streaming cloud stream 1.0
流云流1.0中的功能
right yeah something you can learn about
是的，你可以学到一些东西
and gory detail with me and Mark this
和我一起去细节，并标记这个
afternoon but we're just going to
下午，但我们正要去
quickly show how it works it's going to
快速展示它是如何工作的
be amazing
很棒
so let's do another endpoint we're going
所以让我们做另一个终点
to create another endpoint that respond
创建另一个响应的端点
to posts okay
发表好
post like so and I'll say public void
像这样发帖，我会说公共无效
right and I'll say request body
是的，我会说请求正文
reservation are and I need to make a
预订是，我需要做一个
call to this so one once we do this we
呼吁这一点，一旦我们做到这一点，我们
need to make sure we do histories so I'm
需要确保我们做的历史，所以我
gonna make a call alright to a to my
会打电话给我的
message my messaging bus in this case
在这种情况下向我的消息传递总线发送消息
I'm going to use Redis but we could as
我将使用Redis，但我们可以
easily use a Kafka and rabbim queue
轻松使用Kafka和Rabbim队列
right
对
it's Redis because you included a write
这是Redis，因为您包括写
a dependency right at the beginning
一开始就具有依赖性
right
对
is it still coming today oh the spring
今天春天还会来吗
cloud starters stream Redis so that it's
云启动器流Redis，因此
going to auto wire the connections
将自动接线
between these different services so I
这些不同的服务之间，所以我
can just include them and I bind them I
可以包括它们，我将它们绑定
use the at enable binding annotation so
使用at enable绑定注释，以便
I'm going to go up here to my
我要上去我的
application I'll say that this is going
应用程序，我会说这将会
to be hello at enable binding source
向启用绑定源打招呼
source class okay source class comes
源类还可以，源类来了
from org spring from McLeod stream
从org spring从McLeod流
messaging source it's an interface that
消息源是一个接口
by convention defines a channel that it
按照惯例定义了一个
has a name called output ok so output
有一个名字叫做output，所以输出
what we're doing is my configuration
我们正在做的是我的配置
we're mapping inputs and outputs egress
我们正在映射输入和输出出口
and ingress channels of destinations in
目的地的入口通道
your different services and giving them
您的不同服务并给予他们
a named condo in a pipe and so that
管道中的命名公寓，以便
configuration lives in a config server
配置位于配置服务器中
here right so where's the config server
在这里，所以配置服务器在哪里
here we are a reservation client and you
在这里，我们是预订客户，您
can see that we've said spring cloud
可以看到我们说过春云
stream bindings that output equals
流绑定输出等于
reservations on the other side I'm going
我要去的另一边
to have blah blah blah that input equals
等等等等输入等于
reservation so they're going to agree to
保留，以便他们同意
meet I have a rendezvous with
见面我有一个约会
reservations this kind of service
保留这种服务
discovery by middleware right the
通过中间件发现对
messaging middleware so there's a
消息传递中间件，所以有一个
there's going to be a message queue in
里面会有一个消息队列
Redis a rabbit or calf care depending on
视兔子或小腿而定
what you want to use called something
您想要使用的东西叫做
something something reservations you
一些保留你的东西
don't care what there's something
不在乎有什么
something something is that's the beauty
有些东西就是美丽
of it right so what we did is add an
没错，所以我们要做的是添加一个
annotation and it's going to set up all
注释，它将设置所有
of the queues and infrastructure in the
的队列和基础架构
background so we're going to inject the
背景，所以我们要注入
message channel there this is a spring
消息通道那里是春天
messaging a type it comes from spring
传递来自春天的一种类型
negation it's now part of the spring
否定现在是春天的一部分
framework you also use this when you're
框架，当您
using with dealing with WebSockets for
与处理WebSockets一起使用
example and indeed the largest
例子，的确是最大的
communication technology and what we're
通讯技术和我们
saying is I want this named conduit it
说的是我想要这个命名管道吗
boils down more or less to a Java dot
或多或少地归结为一个Java点
util dot cue behind the scenes by
util点提示由幕后
default but we're going to connect it to
默认，但我们将其连接到
middleware integration adapters and I'll
中间件集成适配器，我将
speak to for example
例如说话
or to Kafka whatever and that happens
或卡夫卡，无论发生什么情况
automatically so you don't have to
自动，因此您不必
really wire that stuff together you just
真的把这些东西连在一起
inject the the client or the the pipe
注入客户或管道
here and you put something in so I'm
在这里，你放一些东西，所以我
going to say this type message channel
要说这种消息通道
that send message builder dot with
发送消息生成器点
payload I'm going to say art I get
有效载荷，我要说的是艺术
reservation name dot build okay and
保留名称点构建好，并且
that's me sending a message for somebody
那是我给某人发送信息
else to consume I'm going to use that to
否则我会用它来消耗
a synchronous asynchronous they receive
他们收到的同步异步
the reservation name and then write it
预订名称，然后写上
okay that look okay to you doc yeah
好吧，你也好吗doc yeah
enjoy this are they ready sale I so we
享受这是他们准备出售我所以我们
can actually state it okay I should do
可以说可以，我应该做
that
那
and I'm going to go also to the service
我也要去服务
itself and do the reverse I'm going to
本身，做相反的事情，我要去
accept new messages on the service so
接受服务上的新消息，以便
here I've done the same thing of that
在这里我做了同样的事情
spring cloud starter stream Redis I'll
春季云启动流Redis我会
bring that back into the play here we
把它带回来玩，我们在这里
are and I'm going to do the at enable
是，我将在启用
binding in Reverse I'll say I'm gonna be
在反向绑定，我会说我会
a sync
同步
no yeah so yeah you are so on the other
不，是的，你是另一个
side so you're a sync on this side in
一边，所以您在这边同步
sources beginning if you don't like
如果您不喜欢的话，源开始
those names if they confuse you which
这些名称，如果他们使您感到困惑，
they will yeah you can make up your own
他们会的，你可以自己做
interfaces call them whatever you want
接口随便你叫什么
you know in and out for example or
你知道进出例如
output and with that in place I can
输出，有了它，我可以
create a messaging endpoint message in
在以下位置创建消息传递终结点消息
point this is a spring innovation type
这是春季创新型
class a message reservation receipt i
给我留言预订收据
before e your English at ease bill I
在您轻松英语之前，我
before E except up to see
在E之前，除了看到
well II IV e artist who's met with my
与我见面的II IV e艺术家
dyslexia okay public void except
诵读困难好吗，公众无效，除了
reservation string RN oops okay and I'm
保留字符串RN哎呀，我是
going to make this a service activator
将其作为服务激活器
that is to say that it's going to be
那就是说它将是
called whenever a message comes in its
每当有消息进入时调用
inversion of control for messaging don't
消息传递的控制反转不
the Hollywood principal don't call me
好莱坞校长不要打给我
I'll call you right so input channel
我会打给你，所以输入频道
equals sync dot input and I'm going to
等于同步点输入，我要
inject the repository that we had here
注入我们在这里拥有的存储库
on the service the reservation
在服务上预订
repository for spring data JPA and I'll
弹簧数据JPA的存储库，我将
just use that to write the data out
只是用它来写出数据
okay so this terrorization repository
好的，所以这个恐怖资料库
that save new reservation RN okay if I
可以保存新的预订RN，如果我
go to the other side I need to make sure
去另一边我需要确保
that I yeah I did that correctly good so
我是的，我做得很好，所以
that looks legit let's try that so we're
看起来合法，让我们尝试一下，
to go back to the reservation service
回到预订服务
restart go back to the reservation
重新开始回到预定
client restart as well
客户端也重新启动
excuse my davids okay and that'll do I
请问大卫的行吗，那我会做
think that fingers crossed we're going
以为我们要走了
to go to the console here open this up
去控制台这里打开
advanced restclient
高级restclient
and I'm going to send an H to be post to
我要寄一个H到
this endpoint and it's going to have
这个端点，它将有
we've already got him we need somebody
我们已经有了他，我们需要一个人
else who wants to play hi name okay how
其他想打个招呼的人好吗
you spell that buddy
你拼那个哥们
k s T e FF yeah cool I think that'll
KS T FF是的，我认为那会
work you're going to be our first victim
工作，您将成为我们的第一受害者
so we're going to post to the API
所以我们要发布到API
gateway at forward slash reservations
斜杠保留处的网关
adjacent document with of type
类型为的相邻文档
application Jason we should hit it if we
应用程序Jason，如果我们
can if it works we should be able to see
可以的话，我们应该能够看到
just reflected here so I'll do that
只是在这里反映出来，所以我会做
let's get this out here okay and here
让我们在这里好好把它拿出来
ready there we are yeah good stuff so
准备在那里，我们是好东西，所以
messaging is working right we're able to
消息传递工作正常，我们能够
read with rest but guarantee rights with
休息阅读但保证权利
messaging CQRS were optimizing for the
消息传递CQRS正在针对
right kind of read and write and we're
正确的读写方式，我们
separating them so we don't use the same
分开他们，所以我们不使用相同的
for both naturally this isn't the same
因为两者自然是不一样的
as it's distributed transaction but you
因为它是分布式事务，但是您
do get state synchronization and it is
确实获得状态同步，这是
guaranteed to work eventually right
保证最终可以正常工作
eventual consistency okay well I want to
最终一致性好吧，我想
I want to make sure that if something
我想确保
does happen to one of my reservation
确实发生在我的预订之一上
services for example if the instances
服务，例如，如果实例
should go down that we recover
应该下降，以便我们恢复
gracefully remember in a sufficiently
优雅地记住
distributed system there is no such
分布式系统没有这样的
thing is 100% highly available in a
事情是100％高可用性的
software instead you want to optimize
您想优化的软件
for time to remediation how quickly can
需要时间进行补救
I recover and can I be graceful when
我会康复，何时能保持优雅
things are down that's what this is
事情就这样了
about is being graceful when things
当事情变得优雅时
happen so I'm going to go back to my my
发生，所以我要回到我的
reservation client here and I see here
预订客户在这里，我在这里看到
that when if I make this call using the
当我使用
rest tip but it's going to do load
休息小费，但它会做负载
bouncing and that'll work for one to end
弹跳，这将一劳永逸
instances right but it won't work for
实例正确，但不适用于
zero if there are no instances
如果没有实例，则为零
registered this is going to blow chunks
注册这将打击大块
things are going to go south and the
事情要往南走，
iPhone will get a stack trace sent back
iPhone将获得回传的堆栈跟踪
to him or maybe an ass cam or the middle
给他，或者一个屁股凸轮或中间
finger or something just unpleasant you
手指或让您不舒服的东西
know so we need to we need to have a
知道所以我们需要有一个
some sort of we want to isolate that
我们想要隔离某种
failure we want to prevent it from
失败，我们要防止它
cascading beyond the the this little
级联超出了这点
limited place we're going to use a
有限的地方，我们将使用
circuit breaker which as you know in a
如您所知，断路器
building is meant to guard that a
建筑是为了保护
failure or an over surge of electricity
故障或电涌过多
doesn't cause an explosion in a fire
不会引起火灾爆炸
which then takes the house down I'd much
然后把房子拆了
rather the circuit breaker open and the
而是断路器断开并且
lights go off then to lose the house for
灯熄灭然后失去房子
a fire right so that's what we're going
火权，这就是我们要去的地方
to do is going to introduce the circuit
要做的就是介绍电路
breaker pattern here using a component
此处使用组件的断路器模式
from Netflix called hystrix I'll say at
来自Netflix的hystrix，我会在
enable circuit breaker and then I'll
启用断路器，然后我将
annotate my my method here I'll say add
在这里注释我的方法，我会说添加
hystrix command fallback method equals
hystrix命令后备方法等于
and I'll pass in a method name here fall
我将在秋天传递一个方法名称
back and all I'm going to do is I'm
回来，我要做的就是
going to return just something simple I
我会返回一些简单的东西
just want to have a useful fallback
只想有一个有用的后备
scenario graceful degradation right
情景优美降级权
Netflix and other big services they do
Netflix及其所做的其他大型服务
this all the time they'll say oh well
他们一直在说哦
this service isn't available but you
此服务不可用，但您
know here's something else so in this
知道这里还有别的东西
case it'll just return an empty list
如果它只是返回一个空列表
okay so this is my reservation client
好的，这是我的预订客户
I've got the I should have that on a
我有我应该在一个
class path maybe ok looks ok so if I go
上课的路径可能还不错，所以如果我去
to the names endpoint again things are
到名称端点再次是
happy so long as the reservation service
只要预订服务就开心
is there but what happens if I now go to
在那儿，但是如果我现在去
the reservation service and you know
预订服务，你知道
take it out of the game like so
像这样将其从游戏中删除
immediately falls back to the empty
立刻掉回空虚
ArrayList right
ArrayList右
resiliency is a is a feature my friend
弹性是我朋友的功能
so so okay I'm going to bring back the
所以好吧，我要带回
reservation service that's one feature I
预订服务是我的一大特色
want resiliency I also want when
想要弹性，我也想要何时
something goes wrong to be able to see
出问题了才能看到
what's happening so you guys had a
发生了什么事，所以你们有一个
textbook when you do to the dashboard
对仪表板进行操作时的教科书
and we also want to do crazy yeah let's
而且我们也想疯狂地做，让我们
get to that okay that so yeah okay
做到那好吧，好吧好吧
service do we have enough time yeah
服务我们有足够的时间吗
we've got time I was thinking we might
我们有时间我在想
even be able to the SSO at the end
甚至可以在最后加入SSO
because I think that there's something
因为我认为有些东西
about your github account that isn't
关于不是的github帐户
working because I tried it here is fine
工作是因为我在这里尝试过
you should I don't know well let's see
你不应该知道吗让我们看看
how far we get can we can we anything
我们能做到多远，我们能做什么
let's see how far we go and we love
让我们看看我们走了多远，我们爱
about okay well edit the video if it
好的，请编辑视频（如果有）
doesn't work yeah this is coming out of
不起作用是的，这是从
YouTube okay
YouTube还可以
services backup things should be healthy
服务备份的东西应该健康
this will eventually recover it takes an
这最终将恢复需要
off 32nd some like that
像这样32
I want to visualize what's happening so
我想想像发生了什么
again if you're building cloud native
如果您正在构建云原生
software here we've got software that is
这里的软件，我们有
resilient to failure if you have a
如果您有能力抗拒失败
platform that's underneath you that's
在你下面的平台是
babysitting your instances it's going to
保姆实例
heal the the application it'll see that
修复应用程序后，它将看到
you've got a failed instance and it will
您的实例失败了，它将
recover it or restore the state so that
恢复它或恢复状态，以便
if you asked for five instances or four
如果您要求五个实例或四个
as this kind of contracted yesterday in
就像昨天签订的合同
the keynote you will get four come heck
主题演讲，您将得到四个
or high water right uh I don't have that
还是高水吧，我没有那个
platform running in my local machine
在我的本地计算机上运行的平台
here but I just restarted it manually so
在这里，但我只是手动重新启动，所以
it's going to recover
它会恢复
that's good that's important you want
很好，很重要，你想要
the platform to where the payment for
付款平台
you and you want your software to play
您和您想要您的软件玩
nicely when that happens I do want the
很好，那时候我确实希望
ability to visualize what's happening
可视化正在发生的事情的能力
though I want to go to see uh you know
虽然我想去看看你知道
where these circuits are where there are
这些电路在哪里
trouble where there's trouble right so
麻烦哪里有麻烦，所以
I'm going to go to startup Spring Rio
我要去Spring Rio创业
and I'll create the history dashboard
我将创建历史记录仪表板
here we are and the in strict dashboard
在这里，我们在严格的仪表板上
is a well just that as a dashboard that
只是作为仪表板而已
you can use to visualize the flow of
您可以用来可视化流程
traffic through circuits in your system
通过系统中电路的流量
I'm going to be using the config client
我将使用配置客户端
naturally and Eureka discovery and
自然而然，尤里卡的发现和
hystrix dashboard or voila and that'll
hystrix仪表板或瞧，那会
do here we go generate Sean finder open
在这里我们去生成Sean finder打开
and this is a very simple app in fact
这实际上是一个非常简单的应用
it's almost artfully so so paste that in
几乎是巧妙地将其粘贴
there
那里
we're going to name it hystrix dashboard
我们将其命名为hystrix仪表板
because I can and I'll remove
因为我可以并且我将删除
application up properties and I'm going
应用程序属性，我要去
to go to demo application I'll say at
去演示应用程序，我会在
enable at an in history dashboard okay
在历史记录仪表板上启用
and we go now this will come up on some
我们现在走了
port I have no idea
港口我不知道
literally no idea where we are now port
根本不知道我们现在在哪里
somebody 8010 I'll buy that localhost
有人8010我要买那个本地主机
8010 forward slash hystrix dot HTML okay
8010正斜杠hystrix点HTML可以
now history start HTML this is a
现在历史记录开始HTML这是一个
dashboard that expects a stream of
期望流的仪表板
information from these circuit breakers
这些断路器的信息
you're gonna have circuit breakers
你会有断路器
throughout your system and they will
遍及您的系统，他们将
emit a heartbeat a service an event
发出心跳服务事件
stream that you can get to from from the
您可以从中获取的流
node localhost
节点本地主机
8050 forward slash hystrix dot stream
8050正斜杠hystrix点流
okay this is server sent events oh don't
好的，这是服务器发送的事件哦，不要
try curling this you'll be there for a
尝试卷曲它，你会在那里
long time you want to paste that into
很长时间您想将其粘贴到
here and you can monitor right you can
在这里，你可以监控，你可以
see this pretty visualization of your
看到您的漂亮可视化
circuit remember my circuit is the rest
记住我的电路是其余的
controller called get reservation names
名为获取保留名称的控制器
I'm going to now move that over here
我现在要把它移到这里
move this over there and let's create
把它移到那边，让我们创建
some traffic and we'll see what happens
一些交通，我们会看到会发生什么
when I create some some activity if I
当我创建一些活动时，如果我
could just find an instance over here
可以在这里找到一个实例
reservation names good so I'm going to
预订名称很好，所以我要
drive traffic on the Left I'm commanding
在我指挥的左边开车
it as fast as my little fingers will let
它的速度就像我的小手指将让
me and you'll see that the visualization
我，你会看到可视化
on the right is more or less real-time
在右边或多或少是实时的
I'm gonna let go now and it's still
我现在要放手，它仍然
refreshing that's how hard i whaled on
令人耳目一新，这就是我捕鲸的辛苦
that and you see it's bursting so it's
那，你看到它破裂了
real time but it's a moving average as
实时，但作为移动均线
traffic drains off the numbers trend
交通流失了数字趋势
downward again great so things are green
再次向下很棒，所以东西很绿色
things are good
事情很好
Green is good spring is green spring is
绿色是美好的春天是绿色春天是
good let's see what happens if something
好，让我们看看如果发生了什么
goes south ok go back to reservation
往南走，可以回去预约
service take it out of the game again
服务再次将其带出游戏
sad but now instant it's red on the
悲伤，但现在瞬间，它在红色
right a hundred percent failure rate and
正确率是百分之一百
eventually that circuit will be
最终，该电路将
officially opened and you can see that
正式开放，您可以看到
that is happening right you get it you
那是正确的，你明白了
get the ability to visualize the flow of
获得可视化流程的能力
data through a system this is just one
系统中的数据只是一个
service right so I'm going to restart my
服务正确，所以我要重新启动我的
reservation service and we'll come
预订服务，我们会来
together
一起
sorry when the circuit is open it went
对不起，当电路断开时，它走了
blue they already see that so red is a
蓝色，他们已经看到，所以红色是
failure
失败
blue is I'm not even going to try yeah I
蓝色是我什至不去尝试，是的，我
know it's down I'm not even going to try
知道它已经失败了，我什至不去尝试
yep and that's what's useful about it
是的，这是有用的
right that's why it's a circuit that's
对，这就是为什么它是一个电路
now of course the key ordering things
现在当然要订购东西了
were good again so we cut off the
又好，所以我们切断了
downstream traffic completely so that
完全下游的交通
we're not going to overwhelm anybody
我们不会让任何人不知所措
further downstream exactly the point
再往下游精确一点
yeah you want to want to prevent the
是的，你想防止
feeling from becoming more than ya
变得不止于雅
handle more than help you I did that for
处理多于帮助您，我做到了
a single node naturally if I have more
如果我有更多的话，自然是一个节点
than one service that uses a circuit
比使用电路的一项服务
breaker I want to visualize an advocate
我想形象化一个倡导者
for that we have the turbine AMQP
为此，我们拥有涡轮AMQP
checkbox here it connects to Rab and Q
复选框，它连接到Rab和Q
and then can aggregates these streams
然后可以汇总这些流
from across different circuits and
来自不同的电路和
different systems into one stream they
他们将不同的系统整合成一个流
don't do that at Netflix and Netflix
不要在Netflix和Netflix上这样做
they just they ask Eureka where all of
他们只是问尤里卡所​​有
the service instances are and then they
服务实例是，然后它们
go and pull the streams from them so we
去拉流从他们，所以我们
do we did it the other way around we we
我们是否以相反的方式做到了
push them to AMQP so there's just one
推他们到AMQP，所以只有一个
place where you just listen to a message
您只听消息的地方
in queue and get all of the streams in
在队列中并获取所有流
one place and that's what that turbine
一个地方，那就是那个涡轮
aim QP is all right tracing tracing now
目标QP现在可以正确追踪
this is another really exciting feature
这是另一个非常令人兴奋的功能
inside of spring cloud brixton which is
春天云布里克斯顿里面是
where do you live by the way which city
你在哪里住哪座城市
I live in Brixton oh no what happened I
我住在布里克斯顿，哦，不，发生了什么事
wonder why I was Kovac at Swindon all
想知道为什么我是史云顿的科瓦奇人
the permutations of letters in the in
中的字母排列
the knowing world anyway um if anybody
无论如何，这个认识的世界
else has a favorite cheap station
否则有一个最喜欢的廉价车站
beginning with C yeah come and talk to
以C开头来和
me later
我待会儿
umm what are the exciting new features
嗯，什么是令人兴奋的新功能
in spring cloud Brixton I did it well
在春天的云彩Brixton中，我做得很好
then well then thank you I used to it um
那好吧然后谢谢你我习惯了
what an exciting new features here is a
这里令人兴奋的新功能是
integration of something called spring
整合了所谓的春天
cloud sleuth Solis who knows what it'll
知道怎么回事的云侦探索利斯
do stays like Sherlock Holmes exactly a
确实像夏洛克·福尔摩斯一样
detective finds we've so we've chosen
侦探发现我们已经选择了
this name
这个名字
somewhat controversially as we said but
正如我们所说有些争议，但
so many people said yeah I like that I
这么多人说是的，我喜欢我
really like that
真的很喜欢
we couldn't which is cooking we couldn't
我们做不到哪做的菜
change it parent is very difficult for
改变它的父母是很难的
Chinese people sorry yeah we're going to
中国人很抱歉，我们要
have to find a nice Chinese character to
必须找到一个不错的汉字来
put on the website that means same thing
放在网站上意味着同样的事情
we didn't mean some words are just
我们不是说有些话只是
unpronounceable and for everybody right
不可发音，适合所有人
we all have words we can't get across so
我们都有一些我们无法理解的话
yeah my five-year-old has trouble with
是的，我五岁了
still these - yeah awkward so anyway um
还是这些-是的，尴尬，所以无论如何
we want this blue and integrate this
我们想要这个蓝色并将其整合
what it does is it provides us
它所做的是为我们提供了
distributed tracing why would you want
分布式跟踪为什么要
that well if I had more than one service
如果我有一项以上的服务
in a distributed system which will I
在分布式系统中
will
将
I want to be able to correlate which
我希望能够关联哪个
requests triggered some sort of output
请求触发了某种输出
in another service if I make a call so
在另一个服务中，如果我拨打电话
from one service to another to another
从一项服务到另一项服务
in the middle one dies I want to see
在中间，我想死
which requests from the first one
第一个请求
triggered the error the second one it's
触发了第二个错误
about it's about relationships it is and
关于关系，并且
it's a little bit about latency as well
这也与延迟有关
people use this for hunting latency bugs
人们用它来寻找延迟错误
very good very useful so we have it's a
非常好非常有用，所以我们有一个
generic abstraction spring cloud sleuth
通用抽象弹簧云侦探
there is a the first implementation is
有一个第一个实现是
based on Zipkin which is from ashley
基于来自ashley的Zipkin
second implementation but anyway yeah
第二实施，但无论如何
first implementation is just logging
第一个实现只是记录
everything goes to stand it out and then
一切都会脱颖而出，然后
you can aggregate it any to any way you
您可以以任何方式将其聚合
want which is actually pretty powerful
想要实际上非常强大的
yeah and we have clients already using
是的，我们已经有客户在使用
that because that's what that was a
那是因为那是一个
contribution right that came from the
来自
for finance guys right hi Marty thank
对于财务人员，您好，Marty，谢谢
you what you guys were here here and
你们在这里的人
then we added up added an abstraction
然后我们加了一个抽象
and implemented the abstraction for this
并为此实现了抽象
is Zipkin thing which is adrian Cole's
是Zipkin的东西，这是Adrian Cole的
baby
宝宝
Adrian joined us recently we might see
Adrian最近加入了我们，我们可能会看到
now on Twitter he'll be here later on
现在在Twitter上，他稍后会在这里
today so if you want to talk to anybody
今天，所以如果你想与任何人交谈
about tracing the guy who basically
关于追踪那个基本上是
wrote the book on it is going to be here
在那本书上写了这本书
later on today so he just joined us from
今天晚些时候，所以他只是从
Twitter yep
是的
and it would be using difference before
它会在之前使用差异
then see the Netflix things that Square
然后看到Netflix的事情
he was pretty much at any any he gets
他几乎可以得到任何东西
around yeah the guy can cloud
是的，那个家伙可以云
against that company so now we've got
针对那个公司，所以现在我们有了
this service and I want it to be traced
这项服务，我希望它可以被追踪
I want message that go do it I can
我想要消息去做，我可以
already see CH right oh yeah on the log
已经在记录中看到CH对哦对
that I've got a log for matter these are
我有一个日志，这些是
empty at the moment but I want I want to
此刻空着，但我想我想
turn them into the actual correlated if
将它们转化为实际的相关
you know they're empty because there's
你知道他们是空的，因为
nothing's happened right right you're
什么都没发生对不对你
just logging the start up tested like
只是记录测试的启动
exactly right
非常正确
so first thing I'm going to do is I'm
所以我要做的第一件事就是
gonna go back to my build here and we
要回到我在这里的建筑，我们
introduce spring cloud starter Zipkin
介绍Spring Cloud Starter Zipkin
and I oh I have to do oh I need to
而且我哦我必须做哦我需要
introduce a sampler a beam of type
向取样器介绍一种类型的光束
sampler now why would I want a specific
现在为什么要采样
type of sampler doctor because it's in
取样器医生的类型，因为它在
the nature of these distributed tracing
这些分布式跟踪的性质
systems people find surprisingly that
系统人们惊讶地发现
there's quite a lot of data that you
你有很多数据
could generate with this kind of thing
可以用这种东西产生
so it's actually completely mandatory to
所以实际上完全是强制性的
have some kind of statistical sample you
有某种统计样本
don't want to collect all the traffic
不想收集所有流量
it's impossible it just it just kills
这是不可能的，只是杀死
any back-end that you're ever going to
您将要使用的任何后端
put in it so there's a thing called the
放在里面，所以有一个叫做
sampler we introduces an abstraction in
采样器中我们引入了一个抽象
spring cloud which basically just at the
春天的云基本上只是在
minute there's only one implementation -
一分钟只有一个实现-
there's one that says always' and one
有一个说总是”和一个
that says never and never is the default
这表示从不，而且从来没有是默认值
and so we just put in always in so that
因此，我们始终将其放入
we're going to get all the traffic but
我们将获得所有流量，但
you could you could add one we will be
你可以，你可以加一个，我们将
adding more so we'll be adding ones that
添加更多，所以我们将添加那些
you can tune at runtime right so you can
您可以在运行时进行正确的调整，这样您就可以
say right I want to sample all the
说正确，我想取样所有
requests from Starbucks man because he's
来自星巴克男人的要求，因为他
an idiot and I want to see what he's
一个白痴，我想看看他是什么
doing
在做
absent that kind of thing and hurt but
缺少那种东西而受伤，但是
in a minute we just we're going to we're
在一分钟内，我们只是要去
just going to get all the traces for all
只是要获取所有的所有痕迹
the data so that we can have a look at
数据，以便我们可以看一下
something run stop and rerun run this
某些东西停止运行并重新运行
will be in the keynote tonight as well
今晚也将在主题演讲中
by the way your own get your eyes peeled
顺便说一句
are you concerning akin to the talk tell
您是否在谈论类似谈话
the person as you're sitting next to
你坐在旁边的人
that viewer the first demo and it is
该观众的第一个演示，它是
there a target plant length one disorder
有目标植物长度的一种疾病
I think Spencer will be going into it
我认为Spencer会参与其中
and his talk tomorrow
和他明天的演讲
okay good perfect so what have I done
好，非常完美，所以我做了什么
I've added the always sampler to both
我已经将始终采样器添加到两者中
the reservation service and the client I
预订服务和客户我
added spring cloud starter Zipkin
添加了春季云启动器Zipkin
actually and main Spencer this afternoon
实际上和今天下午的主要斯宾塞
as well live Wigan it exhaustion so
以及活着的维甘筋疲力尽
there you go so that's on both sides now
你去那里，所以现在两边
I can demonstrate this by going to the
我可以通过转到
reservation client getting the data
预订客户端获取数据
right there's the request in died also
那里的要求也死了
got a rest request and he went off to
得到了休息请求，他去了
the service with another rest request
另一个休息请求的服务
right right so we're expecting to see
对对对，所以我们期待看到
two spans two elements of that two legs
两个跨越那两条腿的两个元素
on the journey
在旅途中
I have Zipkin running on the shell here
我在这里的外壳上运行了Zipkin
and then another note on there's three
再有三个注意
processes there's the web there
那里有网络
collector and the query engine so these
收集器和查询引擎，所以这些
are three things running on the side
侧面有三件事
it's pretty easy to run just great get
运行起来很容易，获得很好
clone the code and then go into the bin
克隆代码，然后进入垃圾箱
directory
目录
it's a Gradle build so you can just do
这是一个Gradle版本，所以你可以做
bin or slash collector pin for slash
bin或斜杠收集器销（用于斜杠）
there at docker images actually that
在码头上的图像实际上
spark was even easier for that okay now
这样，火花就更容易了
let's see if I go to localhost 8080
让我们看看我是否要进入本地主机8080
which is where a Zipkin is running its
Zipkin正在运行
web UI I see this okay you can see it's
网络用户界面，我认为可以，您可以看到
got instances services for both my
为我俩提供实例服务
client and my service they're both here
客户和我的服务他们都在这里
and specific types of circuits are
具体的电路类型是
specific types of traces specific
具体的痕迹类型
ingress and egress points in the
入口和出口点
application or are represented here so
应用程序或在这里表示如此
reservation names I want to see
我想看的预订名称
everything from there to there and this
从那里到那里的一切
is about a minute ago right you can see
大约一分钟前，您可以看到
that I have a reservation service well
我的预订服务很好
here doctor you explain yeah what are we
在这里医生您解释是的，我们是什么
looking at
看着
so yeah the call came in it's like a
是的，打来的电话就像
waterfall right you this a graph with a
瀑布对您来说这是一个带有
time line on it the call came in at the
时间线上的电话是在
top - I can see the path there flash
顶部-我可以看到闪光的路径
names something happened a little bit of
命名某事发生了一点
latency there took almost 60
那里的等待时间接近60
milliseconds before the server on the
服务器上的毫秒数
other side got it all right so you can
对方没事，所以你可以
see that Spanish I think if you click on
看到西班牙语，我想如果您单击
that top one yes sir
那是一位先生
then you can see it's some duplication
然后你会看到它有些重复
going on
继续
why that is we need to sort that out but
为什么那是我们需要解决的问题，但是
look at the top there you can see
看那里的顶部
clients and client received bracketed
客户和收到方括号的客户
around server receive service send and
服务器周围接收服务发送并
said the server has sent back some data
说服务器已经发回一些数据
to this span to say that it got the data
在这个范围内说它得到了数据
and it dealt with it and it sent it back
它处理了它并发回了
again so you can see see a timeline the
再次，这样您就可以看到时间表
terminology here is actually from data
这里的术语实际上来自数据
which is the google google tracing
这是谷歌谷歌跟踪
engine that isn't open source but they
引擎不是开源的，但是他们
published a paper on it that i'm going
发表了一篇我要去的论文
to do it the google right no it's google
做到谷歌的权利，不是谷歌
it everybody uses something a bit like
每个人都使用类似
that so there's it can is def alike
这样就可以像def一样
there's another single h trace which is
还有另一条h迹线是
on head than the head up ecosystem which
比平视生态系统
is slightly different data model but
数据模型略有不同，但
basically it's def a based the only
基本上它是基于def的唯一
problem with that for is that it's very
的问题是，这是非常
RPC focused so it's all about clients
RPC专注于客户
sending and receiving and service
收发服务
telling you that they finish with it
告诉你他们完成了
speaking of sending let's also see what
说到发送，我们还要看看
happens if i you yeah let's do a
发生如果我你是的，让我们做一个
messaging one right one so yeah watch
消息传递一个正确的一个，所以是的
things happen who's already in ER we
发生了什么事，我们已经在急诊室了
need another name naturally so josh all
自然需要另一个名字
the community here and doctor sire
这里的社区和医生父亲
doctor ride peeta peeta with an i will
医生与我会骑佩塔佩塔
Gary my boy Gary okay so Gary there we
加里，我的男孩，加里，好吧，加里，我们
go
走
hit Send there's Gary right so that
点击“发送”，加里（Gary）对，这样
works now we go to Zipkin this one bug
现在工作，我们去Zipkin这个错误
doesn't support the escape button okay
不支持退出键
what do we see now we see that apply to
现在我们看到了什么
you is is what i use its wits about oh
你就是我用它的智慧哦
sorry the UI is why they use it twitter
抱歉，UI是他们使用它的原因
and the newest first reservation client
和最新的第一预订客户
no you want the one that you just good
不，你想要一个你只是好的
night yeah well okay so two rows of aged
晚上好，好吧，两排老
reservations fine traces less than a
保留的痕迹少于一个
minute ago i think that one qualifies
分钟前，我认为有人
yeah
是的
HTTP reservations so this is where we
HTTP保留，所以这是我们的地方
posted the message you can see the
发布消息，您可以看到
headers here at the in yet the you know
标题在这里，但你知道
the when the data came into the system
数据何时进入系统
and then you go down here you see
然后你下去这里你会看到
message
信息
input that's the other side or that the
输入是另一面或
messages came in from Redis would see
来自Redis的邮件会看到
the same kind of messages from Reb MQ or
来自Reb MQ的相同类型的消息或
Kafka header information metadata about
Kafka标头信息元数据有关
the transit there's a little bit of
过境有一点
latency in there can you see that you go
那里的等待时间可以看到你走了吗
back to that step behind yep worth
回到是值得的一步
noting is that we're doing all this
注意我们正在做所有这一切
automatically for you it's interceptors
自动为您拦截
on the rest template on the rabbit
在兔子的其余模板上
template all this stuff yes that's the
模板所有这些东西是的
important thing right I didn't need to
重要的事情，我不需要
do anything I need to change my code all
做所有我需要更改的代码
I did was add a sampler right and look
我所做的就是添加采样器，然后看
at the latency you can see when the post
在等待时间您可以看到帖子
ended at that little blip the white bit
结束了一点点白点
and then the gap of like a few
然后差距像
milliseconds where Redis accepted the
Redis接受的毫秒数
message and then pushed it off with it
消息，然后将其推开
so this is message broker time that's
所以这是消息代理时间
message but if your latency there that
消息，但是如果您的延迟在那里
we can't actually capture yet at least
我们至少还无法捕获
anyway we do care what you can infer
无论如何，我们会在乎您能推断出什么
interesting somebody had a question why
有趣的是有人问为什么
was that yeah oh you miss yeah you get
是的，哦，你想念吗，你得到了
this
这个
in the log section so what is the
在日志部分，那么什么是
correlation ID is the question is the
相关ID是问题
first question can I deal with outfit
我可以处理衣服的第一个问题
yeah so in if you see if you look in the
是的，所以如果你看看你是否看着
log you will see some uu IDs coming up
日志中，您会看到一些uu ID
in the in the log and so there's a
在日志中，所以有一个
there's a trace which is labeled across
上面有条痕迹
the whole of that waterfall and then
整个瀑布然后
each of those bars is a span and a span
这些条中的每一个都是一个跨度和一个跨度
has another UUID what was the second
还有另一个UUID，第二个是
question
题
yeah yeah yeah so the question is if it
是的，是的，问题是
was more than one hop in this in this
在此不止一跳
conversation what would happen I come to
谈话我会发生什么
the keynote yeah are we going to do that
主题演讲是的，我们要这样做吗
tonight oh yeah I mean obviously we have
今晚哦，是的，我的意思是显然我们有
to just pass the all you have to do
只是通过所有你要做的
really essentially let's keep the trace
实际上，让我们继续追踪
ID and send it in headers for the next
ID，并在下一个标题中发送
guy and if he's listening in the right
家伙，如果他在听正确的话
way then he'll pick it up and turn it
然后他会捡起来把它打开
into more information I have well what
了解更多信息，我知道
we're hearing you asking me if Esther
我们听到您问我是否以斯帖
well we were all instead of time are we
好吧，我们都是时间，而不是时间
right so let's before we go before we
是的，所以让我们先出发再出发
take more questions first of all who do
首先要回答更多的问题
you guys think guys a gals yes no maybe
你们认为你们是加尔斯，是的，也许
crazy would you could you would you use
疯了，你能用吗
such a beautiful thing can you see the
如此美丽的东西你能看到吗
use cases word absolutely so be sure to
用例一词绝对正确，因此请务必
check out the balance of the day and the
查看当天的余额和
balance of the show lots of great talks
演出的平衡很多精彩的演讲
on this of course yeah try I'm trying to
当然可以，我正在尝试
enumerate them all business Spencer and
列举他们所有的业务Spencer和
I talking this afternoon on developer
我今天下午在谈论开发商
experience specifically with this stuff
专门体验这种东西
mark and I are talking this afternoon
马克，我今天下午在说话
about spring cloud stream or the
关于春季云流或
messaging will will have Zipkin in the
消息传递中将包含Zipkin
first one there's a keynote tonight
今晚第一个主题演讲
which we've got a demo I think Michael
我想迈克尔有一个演示
Mennella is talking about spring cloud
Mennella在谈论春天的云
data stuff Baxter
数据资料
Marius is talking about spring cloud
马吕斯在谈论春天的云
stream data flow Spring Cup Spring -
流数据流Spring Cup Spring-
spring AX de-evolution root and there's
Spring AX de-evolution的根，还有
all sorts of stuff happening watch out
发生的各种事情要当心
for those in this track and also in the
对于那些在这方面以及在
big data track mainly I wanted to say
大数据跟踪主要是我想说的
thank we bring it out another question
谢谢，我们提出了另一个问题
they're looking for it thank you very
他们正在寻找它，非常感谢
much okay just that's all before you go
好吧，就在您出发之前
you
您